<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160306" date="2016-03-06 10:02:37 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;The day of travel disaster...&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Spring is comin&#x2019; (I hope...)</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Damn time runs... is been over a month since I wrote last. But I guess that just shows I&#x2019;m a busy guy with lots to do... or maybe I&#x2019;m just damn lazy - you decide ;)&#xD;Well either way a lot happened since last time a gave an update on my doings. One of the things I spent my time doing was attending a Astronomical lab course. It&#x2019;s a course which because of the university requirements in the PhD contract is mandatory unless you can come up with a really good excuse/argument for not attending. Unfortunately I couldn&#x2019;t come up with a such, so for 14 days I was bound to a chair at the Landesternwarte from 09:30-17:30 doing &#x2018;lab&#x2019; exercises in astronomy. This doesn&#x2019;t sound that bad since Astronomy is after all what I&#x2019;m doing for a living. And it wouldn&#x2019;t have been if it was actually a laboratory course with experiments you could gain some new knowledge from. Unfortunately &#x2018;lab&#x2019; course down here means pencil/ruler/wikipedia/exercises. Some of the stuff we did was classifying 80 galaxies with a magnifying glass from a photographic plate, measuring the hight of 70 HI line of site profiles of the Milky Way with a ruler to determine the rotation curve of the galaxy and drawing a binary systems orbit(s) on millimeter paper. Excellent tasks to get an insight into and an introduction to the various aspects of astronomy ... if you are a bachelor student - but a complete waste of time for us!! It could be a really nice course if it was actually a laboratory course on a PhD level with experiments involving &#x2018;real instruments&#x2019; instead calculators, rulers and pen and paper. I&#x2019;m not saying that the course was piece of cake, &#x2018;cause it has been some years since I dealt with the introductory stuff, but considering that I did at least 3 of the exercises in my first year in Copenhagen, it&#x2019;s not really what you want to spend your (precious) PhD time doing! Ahh... good to get that off my chest ;)&#xD;Unfortunately I didn&#x2019;t manage to get that much work done during the lab course (you were actually surprisingly &#x2018;thick-headed&#x2019; after 8 hours intensive pen and paper exercises). I however, managed to get the paper I&#x2019;ve been working on for most of my first year down here ready for submission during the lab course, and submitted it to ApJ on the 12th of February. We haven&#x2019;t heard anything from the referee yet so let&#x2019;s hope that (s)he&#x2019;s in a good mood when (s)he reads it! We also posted it on ArXiv so if you are curious you can check it out &lt;a href="http://arxiv.org/abs/1002.2642"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&#xD;Having submitted the paper and getting fed up with the damn lab course I decided to throw a small party a couple of weeks ago. It turned out to be a really great evening and exactly what we needed to get through the last week of &#x2018;lab&#x2019; exercises. Even though it was carnival in Germany on the saturday I invited people over I deliberately chose not to mention it in the invitation (you now theme parties is not really my thing;). Either way a few people showed up in costumes and it was actually quite fun - maybe (some day) I will change my view on theme-parties with costumes - but so far I claim my right to still shake my head of people who like that... ;)&#xD;There are more pics from the paty in my gallery.&#xD;Having gotten rid of some anger and celebrated the paper submission I managed to get through the last week of &#x2018;lab&#x2019;. And it for sure made it easier to know that the week after I was working from Denmark, meaning that I would see Mette again! So on the friday after the last day of the lab course I jumped on a train to the airport around 6 o&#x2019;clock. My travels went smoothly without any delays, long queues or missed trains - well I had to run for my train on Copenhagen main station but I caught it and was at Mette&#x2019;s place just before midnight.&#xD;On Saturday morning we were invited to my cousin&#x2019;s 18th birthday in Nordjylland. I was really looking forward to see that part of the family again (It had been more than a year) so it was frustrating to hear  friday night that it might be cancelled because of a snow storm approaching the country. Luckily my parents decided to go either way and they picked me up at Mette&#x2019;s place saturday morning. Mette had to work and my brother was preparing for his yearly ski-trip so it was only the three of us going. We spent like four ours at my uncle and aunt&#x2019;s before the snow more or less forced us to drive back in the afternoon, if we didn&#x2019;t wanted to be stuck in the middle of nowhere. North of &#xC5;rhus most of the snow was gone (on the road) and we were home around 21:00. The rest of the week in DK went with working 9-17 (I just worked when Mette was working) and of course just chillin&#x2019; and enjoying being with Mette for a whole week. We also went to see one of our friend&#x2019;s art exhibition (&lt;a href="http://sarahbodilhansen.blogspot.com/"&gt;check her stuff out at her blog&lt;/a&gt; - she makes some really cool stuff) and checked out the new IKEA in Odense. This sunday it was then time to head back to Germany - and what a day to do that on...&#xD;I had to catch a flight in Copenhagen at  17:40 meaning that I had a ticket to the train from funen at 14 o&#x2019;clock. At noon Mette and I were having lunch an heard that there was a bomb threat on Roskilde station, meaning that my train would not be able to continue to CPH. I called DSB and they just told me to take the train and hope that things were over when we arrived in Roskilde. Luckily they were, but because of queue towards CPH the train company send me to the airport with a cab - that was really nice of them. I then thought that everything was fine, but while I was in the cab I got a text from Scandinavian airlines saying that my flight had been cancelled DAMN IT! I arrived at the airport not knowing whether I could go home or not. Luckily SAS managed to put in another plain so I basically left at the scheduled time. I guess the reason for the cancellation was the storm over Frankfurt (come on not on the same day!). At least we had to get some extra fuel on before we could leave DK because there would be some &#x2018;hanging-around&#x2019; above Frankfurt. Land in FRA was rather interesting experience - I don&#x2019;t think I have experienced that much turbulence before... it&#x2019;s actually quite fun when you will the plain in free fall :) Safely on the ground I rushed to the long distance train station to catch my train to Heidelberg. But the glass roof over the tracks had been damaged so the station was closed... luckily the underground regional station was still working. But because of the storm in Germany ALL trains were extremely delayed. I managed to catch a train towards Heidelberg which was &#x2018;only&#x2019; 240 minutes delayed. And because of that the train was crowded like hell and took twice as long to arrive at Mannheim station where I had to change for the last leg of my travel... what more could go wrong - well they cancelled the first S-train but luckily I managed to catch the next one (after waiting 40 minutes in the cold). But after all I managed to get home and survived a bomb threat, a cancelled flight and a storm... The day of travel disaster!!&#xD;Well safely back in HD I have been working full time this week. Not much to report, except that I booked flights and signed up for a &lt;a href="http://www.astro.psu.edu/firstgalaxies/"&gt;conference&lt;/a&gt; in june where we hope to give a talk about our paper on QSO variability selection. But the amount of talks to participants is really limited, so my fingers are crossed. The conference is in State College, Pennsylvania, which is only a 4 hours drive from New York. I therefore extended my stay with a couple of days so I can fulfill one of my &#x2018;dreams&#x2019; and explore New York City by foot - DAMN it&#x2019;s gonna be nice!!!&#xD;So until then I just have to enjoy spring (if it ever arrives - woke up this morning to snow chaos... come on it&#x2019;s f*ing march!) and get my ELIXIR/JWST project running, while I find some cool lensed quasars in Stripe 82 ;)&#xD;Till next time&#xD;Kasper</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Saturday, 6 March 2010&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="6_Spring_is_comin_%28I_hope...%29_files/shapeimage_2.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="400px" height="300px"/>
</content>
