<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160306" date="2016-03-06 10:02:45 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Thanks...giving&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Back to &#x2018;everyday life&#x2019;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>I got back safe and sound from Leiden a couple of weeks ago. Since then life he in SB has been pretty busy. Basically right after I got back Mette and I got our first visit from DK. Mette&#x2019;s Cousin SS passed by. She didn&#x2019;t come directly from DK, as she&#x2019;s spending a couple of months on Hawaii at a language/athletics-school of some kind. They got the week around thanksgiving off and she therefore decided to fly over an say hi. She arrived safely early sunday. Tuesday Mette and her took the bus to L.A. On the wednesday we went to our first UCSB college-basket game. It was Gauchos against UC San Diego, but despite the local team-up there was not a huge turnout as it was the wednesday before thanksgiving. That aside it was a pretty good match (Gauchos won) and the hotdogs were awesome - nothing like trashy food at sports events :)&#xD;&#xD;Originally Mette and I didn&#x2019;t plan anything special for thanksgiving as we were just expecting to be the two of us. But with SS&#x2019;s visit we decided to go all-in and do the whole shebang. I therefore googled &#x2018;traditional thanksgiving dinner&#x2019; and basically cooked what came up. When we realized what such a dinner actually includes we decided to go for a long walk before engaging in the feast. We went to the old mission here in Santa Barbara. I was there the first time I visited so I knew we were in for a treat. And as the weather was gorgeous it turned out to be a great trip. We also passed by the museum of natural history to see the blue way skeleton they have put on display outside - pretty impressive! When we got back the ladies rented Pretty Woman on the Apple TV, as they wanted to re-live their day in L.A. through the eyes of a &#x2018;champagne girl&#x2019; from the nineties... I guess. Well while they were enjoying a combo of cosy rugs, ice cream, Roberts and Gere I enjoyed my new gas stove, a couple of beers (I needed beer for the gravy so I had no choice but drink the rest) and lots of cooking. We ate around 8p.m. (rather late for a usual thanksgiving dinner - but at least it was dinner and not lunch) and the food turned out pretty darn good if I must say myself. Of course there are improvements to be made next year, but for a first timer I&#x2019;m pretty satisfied... and most importantly so were the girls.&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;After a couple of days off around thanksgiving SS flew back to Hawaii sunday. That also meant that Mette and I could get back to our daily life with the little twist that we were quickly heading towards December. The whole thanksgiving week the weather was great, but basically all of last week it was gray and foggy with quite some rain (SB-standard). This wasn&#x2019;t actually that bad as it made it seem more wintery and all the christmas decorations going up after thanksgiving didn&#x2019;t seem that weird... even though we still have to get used not wearing thick clothes in December. Last friday we also went to the yearly christmas parade here in Santa Barbara to get the christmas spirit going even more. It was apparently the 60th anniversary. Nice tradition - nothing spectacular but very cosy... and there was firetrucks, cheerleader, marching bands and an old police car;)&#xD;&#xD;Oh yeah and we bough bikes! It&#x2019;s so great not to be dependent on walking around, but actually having the possibility of just jumping on the bike. We exploited that last weekend where we went to the market and to whole foods in just less than ~3 hours. The bike ride to whole foods itself only took half the time the (long) frequent bus takes. So the new bikes are definitely worth the money!&#xD;&#xD;This week has been pretty quiet - just working, running a bit and enjoying good food in the evenings. Tonight I&#x2019;m spending the evening and night at the University (sorry Mette) as AS and PJM have a run at &lt;a href="http://keckobservatory.org"&gt;Keck&lt;/a&gt; and I&#x2019;m chiming in. Hence, I&#x2019;m not actually actually observing I&#x2019;m just sitting in as preparation for later this month and next year where we have time on Keck and are doing our own observations, which I&#x2019;m really looking forward to. So far the night has been okay. A couple of hick-ups, but nothing AS and PJM couldn&#x2019;t handle... but now some clouds are unfortunately moving in (hence some time to blog). Let&#x2019;s see how goes.&#xD;&#xD;Cheers&#xD;K&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Saturday, 8 December 2012&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="7_Back_to_everyday_life_files/shapeimage_3.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="477px" height="307px"/>
</content>
