<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20121225" date="2012-12-26 03:44:20 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Okay - I&#x2019;m a geek...&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>TBBT - thumbs up big time!</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>How every one doing? Enjoying 1001?&#xD;Since last time I wrote nothing spectacular have happened. I have mostly use the time at work, but have also had time to socialize a bit in the cold and moist Heidelberg with friends and colleagues. A couple of weeks ago we went to Mannheim to see the 3D version of Avatar. In Germany we are in the unfortunate situation that all movies and tv are dubbed into german or there is an annoying speaker translating everything in to german - even in the cinemas, so we had to go to Mannheim to see the movie in english... and so we did. And WHAT a movie!! The story is not that exciting and without the 3D+special effects the movie would in my opinion just be an ordinary movie about some space-science-fiction-stuff and large blue aliens. People have even compared the content of the movie with &lt;a href="http://pics.blameitonthevoices.com/012010/small_pocahontas%20avatar.jpg"&gt;Pocahontas&lt;/a&gt; and I must agree that the stories are pretty similar. BUT; Avatar is not just an ordinary movie (at least when it is watched in a 3D cinema). It&#x2019;s setting the new standard for movies in the cinema and really gives you a technology wake up call! I was really sceptic about the 3D before I went, and the first 20-30 min I was not really impressed, but then they stopped the movie, said they had some problems with the effects, 15 minutes went by and the fired it up again - this time with the right polarization... and BAM - that&#x2019;s God damn amazing - I&#x2019;m really impressed. The fact that everything was clearer and more alive really gives you a special experience, and of course the paradise-landscapes on Pandora helped a lot. It really felt like you were rushing through the forest with the Avatars... I&#x2019;m really looking forward to more movies in 3D. It MUST be the new thing - and will for sure drag people back to cinemas again.&#xD;Besides watching Avatar we also went out for a couple of dinners the last couple of weeks. Nothing fancy but just to do something instead of working 24/7 in the weekends as well.&#xD;A couple of days ago I started watching the first two seasons of &#x2018;&lt;a href="http://www.cbs.com/primetime/big_bang_theory/"&gt;The Big Bang Theory&lt;/a&gt;&#x2019;, which is an american sitcom about a bunch of scientist at Caltech which are having problems with &#x2018;da ladies&#x2019; and life in general - and DAMN it&#x2019;s funny. I feel like an idiot, sitting alone in my apartment and laughing my ass off... but they really hit something. The thing is, that there is A LOT of geeky jokes and a lot of the stuff they are doing and saying (of course taken to the extremes) is exactly like looking into my head somtimes... so I guess I am a geek/nerd after all (yes Julian, we have to admit that both words apply to us!) - well I already knew it, but TBBT is a good underlining of it. I think I have to take Mario on his word and convince the other guys to find a weekend where we can do a marathon... maybe we should put down some drinking rules?! Well either way TBBT is one of the funniest sitcoms I have seen for a long long long long time! So if you have just a small nerd you are trying to hide, or you love to see us fuck the &#x2018;daily&#x2018; life up in the weirdest way, then have a look at TBBT. Apparently they have signed with CBS for four seasons and the 3rd is still running in the states, so there is plenty of good stuff left - me like!&#xD;Besides drinking, eating and watching tv I have also started running again. I had a break of a couple of weeks since Oxford and Xmas came up. It was a bit tough the first time after christmas, but now I&#x2019;m back on track. I have also started basket again. Don&#x2019;t know id I have mentioned it before, but I play basket every friday night with some guys from the institute. After christmas I bought myself a pair of new shoes which have tested a couple of times now. Last friday (well mostly saturday) I discovered muscles I didn&#x2019;t know I had and this friday I received a minor blue, so yeas I&#x2019;m giving it max in my new shoes - and they are awesome. I have the right gear now (I almost look pro), if just my playing was in the same quality as my outfit I would be great - but either way it&#x2019;s a lot of fun and I&#x2019;m already looking forward to next friday!  &#xD;Hmmm what else has happened since last time... not really much I think...&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;Nope sorry - that was it for this time!&#xD;Talk to you next time.&#xD;Cheers&#xD; </richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Sunday, 24 January 2010&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="24_TBBT_-_thumbs_up_big_time%21_files/shapeimage_2.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="400px" height="300px"/>
</content>
