<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160306" date="2016-03-06 10:02:41 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Not bad - not bad at all!&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Damn that was a tough one...</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Cheers people - I write to you as a new person... or at least I thought it would be like that, but I still feel like my good old self. I guess passing the PhD defense doesn&#x2019;t make you a different person. Nevertheless, I&#x2019;m pretty ecstatic about having made it so far - 2012 has been a pretty tough year work-wise, but being on the other side with a (well earned I believe ;) degree is definitely worth it all. The last several weeks have been long and I have been trying to stuff as much astrophysics into my head as possible. Besides that I had to prepare a 20 minute presentation of the last 3-4 years of work for the (closed) 90 minute defense &#x2018;interrogation&#x2019;. This made a significant fraction of the week before the 9th pass by as shown above: rehearsing in a cloud of chalk dust. It was suggested to me to actually record the rehearsals (making the video above possible)... pretty weird to see oneself giving a blackboard presentation the first time, but it is definitely recommendable as a preparation tool. You really see what and when you screw up watching it on video afterwards. The morning and early afternoon on the 9th (I was defending at 1400 hours) were horrible - but I try to tell myself that I perform better with a bit of nerves and adrenalin rushing through my vanes (no need to have that much next time though) - hopefully that was the case this time as well. Despite the nerves and the long days and many hours in front of the the mac, books and blackboard the last several months, in the end everything worked out and I got what I came for! Not bad - not bad at all.&#xD;&#xD;The next couple of weeks I will mostly try to make sure that my work is ready to move with me into my new life as a postdoc and then of course be celebrating that I made it this far! :D&#xD;&#xD;Now Mette and I can fully look forward to and start preparing the next step in our lives - California here we come!!&#xD;&#xD;Talk to you soon...</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Wednesday, 11 July 2012&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
