<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160306" date="2016-03-06 10:02:40 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Bored... Nope! &#xD;Just Extra Time For Myself&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Post-hand-in-vacuum</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&#xD;So that's what vacuum feels like. It was kind of a weird feeling handing in the thesis last monday. As I wrote last time I was in good shape up to the submission and even had the evening off the day before. In the morning Mette arrived and we went into the city where I had to hand over the thesis to my second referee. Afterwards we spent a couple of days enjoying my freedom and the German spring, which really showed itself from it's best side. Approximately 25 degrees and sun every day last week. Great to be able to sit outside at restaurants again - the dark cozy german restaurants are fine when it is freezing outside but I would any day swap it for lunch and/or dinner outside. However, some great days with Mette here it was kind of weird getting back to 'normal' life. As if something is missing - not that I actually miss the thesis, but for quite some time I always had that to keep me occupied, now it's kind of like a vacuum where there is almost too much time left... good that we had a 3D-HST videocon./Skype meeting this week to keep me occupied ;) But it is however pretty need not to constantly semi-stress.&#xD;&#xD;Last friday the Ice hockey world championship started so I have steadily been following Denmark's matches with the hope that they would make it to the quarter finals. But after the over-time loss to italy sunday I've definitely readjusted my expectations; now they just have to stay in the A-league. Tomorrow we will face Germany, which is hopefully resulting in 3 points on the danish account so we can get away from the damn last place in the group... fingers crossed.&#xD;&#xD;Another thing... I want &lt;a href="http://www.beoplay.com/Products/BeoplayA3#highlights"&gt;this one&lt;/a&gt;! The 'discount' B&amp;O brand B&amp;O play has made the most awesome iPad doc - If the sound is really as good as they claim this is definitely a must have. Especially when/if I get a new iPad over-there with enough space for my music - then it's a neat stereo... me like!&#xD;&#xD;Now I just have to spend a couple of days tying loose ends at work before I can spoil myself in Berlin... and I already did. I have booked a snobby lunch next friday that I'm really looking forward to - I'm a sucker for good food :D&#xD;&#xD;See you around&#xD;Kasper</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Friday, 11 May 2012&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="11_Post-hand-in-vacuum_files/shapeimage_2.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="329px" height="285px"/>
</content>
