<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160306" date="2016-03-06 10:02:30 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Xmas comin' up!</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Plus degrees, wet, dark, and &#x2018;non-cozy&#x2019; describes the feeling down-hill, but the direct opposite applies for the surroundings of the institute up-hill. The snow have bin lying there for a couple of weeks (on-off though), but it&#x2019;s really nice going up there in the mornings. The only bad thing about it is that going from the bus stop to the institute is like a death trap... I don&#x2019;t know why, but for some reason they don&#x2019;t find it necessary to salt a remove the snow all the way to the institute. But besides that the white landscape really brings the christmas spirit up in me - to bad I have to enjoy from my desk;)&#xD;Besides working (which I do most of the time) I went to a couple of parties last weekend. The IMPRS (International Max Planck Research School) held a christmas party last friday and after that Mario threw a party at his place together with his roommates. The IMPRS party was nothing official... we just went to the Mac Planck Haus where we drank a couple of beers and some gl&#xFC;hwein. People were encouraged to to bring some food from their home countries so that we could set up a buffet. There were a lot of nice stuff (some of which i don&#x2019;t what was) such as Indian rice &amp; curry, Italian lasagna, American jam &amp; peanut butter sandwiches, homemade tiramisu etc. Probably I should also have brought something (except from my great spirit;). Maybe next year... wonder if people would like rugbr&#xF8;d with sylte and mustard?&#xD;After the IMPRS party we took the tram to Marios. The apartment were already rockin&#x2019; when we arrived. There were a lot of people (mostly germans - I think) and booze. In germany they have custom that santa arrives on the 6th of december and when he does people give each other presents. This Mario and his roommates made into a gimmick so we all brought a small present which we threw in a large sack when we arrived. When the clock stroke midnight we could then all draw a present from the sack. I bought a small bottle of Absinthe for the sack, which I think was an excellent present for a party gimmick - unfortunately I didn&#x2019;t get it my self. Instead I got a bottle of (cheap) redwine, but at that moment I wasn&#x2019;t really able to judge the quality (of anything). An since I&#x2019;m such a polite and nice person I wouldn&#x2019;t insult the person who bought the present by not drinking it. Maybe not the best decision, but you know how it is making decisions with alcohol in the blood. We were a couple of guys who stayed there to the bitter end. Of course Mauricio and I missed the last bus back to Heidelberg (Mario lives at Eppelheim, a small village/city west of Heidelberg) so we had to take a cab. Luckily it wasn&#x2019;t that expensive, and then I was driven directly to my door which is also preferable after a long night out.&#xD;Tuesday and wednesday I was a &#x2018;fly on the wall&#x2019; at a meeting with all the &#x2018;top-guys&#x2019; of the NIRSpec project. Part of this project is a the collaboration ELIXIR which is paying my salary (from this month - so haven&#x2019;t got my first paycheck from the ELIXIR project yet). It was really interesting but also quite tough since I was the only person who wasn&#x2019;t fully into the NIRSpec and what it&#x2019;s all about. But it what definitely a good crash course into the stuff I&#x2019;m (also) going to work with for the next 3 years. It&#x2019;s gonna be hard but exciting and interesting on the same time.&#xD;Well... just cleaned the apartment and am now just chillin&#x2019; in front of the television. Don&#x2019;t think I&#x2019;m going to work &#x2018;till tomorrow... maybe read a bit tonight but not more than that;)&#xD;&#xD;Merry christmas and happy new year (I&#x2019;m not sure I&#x2019;ll be writing more in 2008 - but you never know!)&#xD;&#xD;see ya&#xD;Kasper&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Saturday, 13 December 2008&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
