<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20121225" date="2012-12-26 03:44:24 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Euro 2012 - It&#x2019;s on!&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Unbelievable... amazing!</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Holland 0 - Denmark 1 !!! Hell YEAH!!!&#xD;&#xD;Holy crap that was a crazy match! It was definitely the longest second half ever. Good that I had my mental trips to Isle of Jura to calm my nerves... I don&#x2019;t know if it was &#x2018;deserved&#x2019; but if they can&#x2019;t score it is pretty hard to win! The tune in the YouTube clip below was played immediately after the win on the danish national radio. The text is something like:&#xD;&#xD;&#x201C;&lt;i&gt;Holland is on hash, Holland is on hash. Now it&#x2019;s 1-0. Orange bong-heads it was an own goal. Holland is on hash. What&#x2019;s up Holland you want a tackle? You&#x2019;re half bald guys on the pitch... we&#x2019;re not afraid of Van Persie and Robben their bodies are filled with skunk and hash and we&#x2019;re on top. In Scotland they have a lot of cool clans. In Holland they only have crappy Tulips... Holland is on Hash... it&#x2019;s 1-0&lt;/i&gt;&#x201C; (freely translated). &#xD;&#xD;A good laugh, but also pretty cocky ;) But what the heck. We won against Holland! A victory against Holland pretty much makes the Euro 2012 a success! Getting through from the group stage would be oretty awesome, though.&#xD;&#xD;1 down 2 to go - we are ready for you Portugal and Germany!&#xD;&#xD;I guess this makes me ready for tomorrow when the last stretch for the PhD defense sets in with reading, reading and more reading.&#xD;&#xD;BS&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Saturday, 9 June 2012&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="9_Unbelievable..._amazing%21_files/shapeimage_2.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="295px" height="375px"/>
</content>
