<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160306" date="2016-03-06 10:02:31 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Back in business</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Well... January is well underway and I&#x2019;m back in Germany after a couple of weeks in Denmark over christmas. For christmas I went to northern Jutland to visit some family with my parents and brother. We were only there for around 24 hours, but it was really nice to see the family - I think it has been like 6 months or so. We had a lot of excellent traditional danish food and some beers, wine and snaps with that - I love danish traditions;) Christmas eve we went around the christmas tree and exchanged presents. I got a lot of cool stuff, among this a new camera - really cool - so I hope that there will be a lot more &lt;a href="perma://BLPageReference/AF9C0EDF-02BF-4792-9553-E5833AAC79A6"&gt;cool pics&lt;/a&gt; in the future.&#xD;When we came back to Funen where my parents and parents &#x2018;in law&#x2019; live there was no time for me to just sit down and relax. First there was a family lunch at Mette&#x2019;s parents. It was nice also to see them, now that I was back in DK. We had a &#x2018;package-game&#x2019; where I was lucky not to get the &#x2018;hate-present&#x2019; which is a 30 cm plastic pixie for the garden, which is really ugly even though it might have enjoyed a year in Germany... well I&#x2019;m glad I didn&#x2019;t &#x2018;win&#x2019; it - sorry for you Birgit :)&#xD;The day after we had christmas lunch at my parents place together with my uncle and ant. We had a lot of food and snaps and people got a bit drunk (read: quite drunk). But it was great seeing them again. Unfortunately my cousins couldn&#x2019;t come. Especially Nik I haven&#x2019;t seen for like... 2-3 years so it would be nice to see him again - maybe next year!&#xD;At as if it wasn&#x2019;t enough I had a third lunch with my high school classmates. We still see one another more less twice a year for a summer party and a christmas lunch which is really cool. This year Mette P. (again, which we all really appreciate) held the party and we were quite a lot that showed up. We again ate and drank a lot (yeat another hurray for danish traditions and pork) and had a really good time - Thanks everybody, and hope you were not to bad the next day Bille ;)&#xD;After having seen most of the family and many of old friends Mette and I went back to Copenhagen to celebrate new years eve with some other friends. Mette had to work a couple of days during christmas and new years eve, which I then used to do a bit of work and to meet with Jacob and a couple of my friends from University of Copenhagen. New years eve was really great - not a huge monkey-party, but really down to earth with great food and good friends - that&#x2019;s how it&#x2019;s suppose to be!&#xD;In the beginning of January Mette and I just enjoyed the last days together before I had to go back to Heidelberg. I came back on the 5th and have since then just tried to get into gear again. For some reason I always feel tired and exhausted after a couple of weeks of. This time I however think there was a good reason - it can&#x2019;t be healthy with so much pork and alcohol in only 14 days!&#xD;But eventually I succeeded to get into gear and the work is going great. I have a lot to do since I&#x2019;m leaving for the states February 7, and since they want me to give a talk there and I have an upcoming IMPRS talk I&#x2019;m not bored! I&#x2019;m not sure I&#x2019;ll have the time to right once more before I leave for &#x2018;The Land of God&#x2019;, but I&#x2019;ll try to keep you updated from there.&#xD;&#xD;Cheers &amp; a late happy 2009&#xD;Schmidt&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Sunday, 18 January 2009&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
