<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160306" date="2016-03-06 10:02:36 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Science &amp; Race Cars&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Xmas is very soon - and I think it&#x2019;s gonna be white!!</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>So as I mentioned last time I updated my blog I have been working quite a bit  the last couple of months since last week I had to go to the first yearly meeting of the ELIXIR collaboration, which was held in Oxford, UK. The purpose of the meeting was first of all to meet the rest of the collaboration, secondly to be introduced to the instrument(s) and then to introduce everyone to the projects we, the students,  are involved in. For those who are interested I&#x2019;m doing a study of the early Universe galaxy dynamics with NIRSpec&#x2019;s IFU on the &lt;a href="http://www.jwst.nasa.gov/"&gt;JWST&lt;/a&gt;. We want to create mock observations with NIRSpec and from that quantify what NIRSpec will be capable of when it&#x2019;s operational (hopefully) in 2014. Can we resolve merger velocity fields and can we tell a merger from an &#x2018;ordinary&#x2019; galaxy at high &lt;i&gt;z&lt;/i&gt; with NIRSpec, are some of the questions we want to answer. I presented the work and plan for this project on the meeting. I went well (it was only a 10+5 min talk) ad I got some good questions - so that was cool.&#xD;The meeting itself was not that long. I arrived a my bed and breakfast called Parklands at wednesday night around 19:00. The part of the meeting where the students were suppose to join started thursday at noon and lasted until friday afternoon - so it was actually only a day and a half but they managed to pack the program tightly, so all students (we were 9 at the meeting I think) gave talks, there were invited speakers given talks on various topics and the PIs presenting the JWST and NIRSpec itself. But the meeting was really good and it was awesome to meet the other students - now I know I&#x2019;m not alone with the ELIXIR stuff. At MPIA it&#x2019;s only Hans-Walter and me who are directly involved in the ELIXIR collaboration, so it can be a bit lonely sometimes. But now I know who and where the other people are, which is great!&#xD;When I arrived wednesday I had arranged that Joakim dropped by Parklands, since he had been around Oxford since the sunday before. Btw. speaking of Parklands... it deserves a couple of words. I guess it is an upper class bed and breakfast which is located 15 min walk north of the astrophysics department. I bet it is how most bed and breakfasts look in the UK but it had a special atmosphere and the english breakfast I enjoyed (while eating it;) two out of three mornings was excellent. An that combined with the nice weather - yeah believe it or not the sun was actually shining from a clear blue sky - and the squirrels playing in the trees outside the window in the mornings, made my stay there pretty cool... but I&#x2019;m glad I didn&#x2019;t have to pay for it myself;)&#xD;Well back to wednesday night. So Joakim and I went out to a typical English restaurant, which means we went to an Indian restaurant were we had something to eat and drink, while catching up. I think last time we saw one another was just before I moved to germany, so it has been a while. One of Joakim&#x2019;s colleagues joined at the restaurant and afterwards we went for a pint in one of the hundreds of pubs in Oxford - me like;) - well I like the pubs, but the flat and warm ale is not really my cop of tee; I could get use to it though but I&#x2019;m not sure I want to.&#xD;Thursday the hosts had arranged for a &#x2018;conference dinner&#x2019; which was again at an Indian place - this place was actually better than the place we went wednesday, except that they put a bit too much coriander in their dishes to my taste - we had a banquet and there was coriander in almost every dish. But besides that it was a really nice evening, where I got to now my new colleagues a bit better. Afterwards we again went for a pint and a whiskey in the closet pub.&#xD;Friday most people left directly after the meeting. One of the professors from Oxford gave some of us a short guided tour of Oxford while the sun was setting (you can actually manage cover the whole of Oxford in less than 2 hours). He showed us some of the important/interesting buildings and colleges, for instance  one of the copyright libraries in England, which has a copy of ALL books published in the UK in there basement!! He also took us to Christ Church College dining hall, better know as the dining hall of Hogwarts, which was really spectacular - not because it&#x2019;s from the Harry Potter movie, but because of the atmosphere and the fact that it is still in use - awesome place!&#xD;&#xD;Friday night I went out for dinner with Nils, one of my good high school mates who lives in Oxford, his sister and girlfriend. We wet to and AWESOME tapas place where we had some sangria, good wine and an excellent dinner. When I met with him he told me to my joy that he had managed to convince his boss to let him gives a guided tour at his work sunday - DAMN NICE. Nils is educating himself as racing engineer and at the moment he is working at the formula one team Force India. Usually they don&#x2019;t give tours since the place is more or less top secret (they have 24-7 guards and don&#x2019;t use keys - only fingerprints) but he somehow managed to convince his boss. Maybe because it was a geeky astrophysicist and his own sister he had to show around; don&#x2019;t know. There were some offices and areas we were not allowed to see but we saw most of the place and some real F1 cars - not just exhibition models in plastic - no the &lt;i&gt;real &lt;/i&gt;deal! Force India lies just across the road of Silverstone race track so we also got a glance of that.&#xD;Saturday night we made a mexican dinner and a bunch of caipirinhas before we went out whit some of Nils friends to dance the night away. I flew back to germany sunday afternoon after a really nice stay in Oxford.&#xD;The last couple of days I have tried to get some things done before the holidays - I don&#x2019;t think I will manage completely so I probably need to work a bit the next couple of weeks, but I am for sure looking forward to a couple of weeks in dk... which is covered in half a meter of snow at the moment! That&#x2019;s been a while - if we are lucky it will stay until the 24th... the weather forecast look good. Just don&#x2019;t hope that it will affect my travels!&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;I will not send out christmas cards this year (either), so take this blog entry as this years christmas card from Heidelberg!&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;Have a nice christmas and a happy new year :)&#xD;Talk to you in the new year!&#xD;Kasper&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;Btw. there are more pictures from Oxford in my &lt;a href="http://gallery.me.com/kasperschmidt#100249&amp;bgcolor=black&amp;view=carouseljs&amp;sel=0"&gt;web gallery&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;... they are so nice and fluffy ...&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Saturday, 19 December 2009&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="19_Xmas_is_very_soon_-_and_I_think_its_gonna_be_white%21%21_files/shapeimage_2.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="400px" height="321px"/>
</content>
