<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160306" date="2016-03-06 10:02:36 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Gl&#xFC;hwein &amp; lebkuchen &#xD;Xmas is here!&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Christmas Joy... soon</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>The last couple of weeks christmas has shown its plastic, &#x2018;musak&#x2019;, chilled, fat face over Germany. It&#x2019;s not that it&#x2019;s a bad thing I&#x2019;m just acknowledging and praising that it is only one month (well 2 if you count from when the stores start decorating) a year. This year the christmas celebration started for real when we had the first gl&#xFC;hwein at the christmas market on the 25th. With that I of course had a bratwurst in br&#xF6;tchen and a feuerwurst... that part of the Heidelberger christmas I really like. Unfortunately I have only been to the christmas market once, since I&#x2019;m pretty loaded with work, caused by a meeting coming up next week. As I have mentioned I&#x2019;m funded by the ELIXIR collaboration, and next week we are having the first annual meeting in Oxford. I therefore have to prepare a small 10 min. talk on my science the last year. It&#x2019;s not a problem at all to put together 5-6 slides from the last year. A lot of cool stuff have come out so no worries there - it&#x2019;s more to select the best parts, and be as prepared as possible... well, you know me :) So I have been working on that full time the last couple of weeks, so only gl&#xFC;hwein once - so far!&#xD;Not to get completely crazy from staring into my screen 24-7 I have also been enjoying myself with a couple of dinners with good friends - this is really the best way to stress down (I can&#x2019;t run every day...). Do instance we went out for a real christmas dinner yesterday. We decided that we wanted to have some goose. The plan was to get drunk at M&amp;M&amp;G&#x2019;s yearly christmas party friday, but unfortunately they had to move to next friday where I&#x2019;m in Oxford HMRF :( so we decide to go out for dinner yesterday instead. We went to this place serving goose and ordered a round of poultry and some good red wine and dug in. Unfortunately they only had one quarter-goose left. The piece of meat seemed to be the same as the &#x2018;leg&#x2019; dish but the &#x2018;side-dishes&#x2019; were MUCH better for the quarter. We ordered the quarter as a shared plate, and luckily I seemed to be to only one interested in the cinnamon red cabbage, gravy and kn&#xF6;del... so instead of the way to salty kraut-sausage-tomato thingy that they served with the goose leg I had a nice great dinner with red cabbage, gravy and potatos... and lot&#x2019;s of goose of course. Afterwards we went out for some cocktails and just enjoyed ourselves. Today have been pretty relaxing. Have worked a bit, but besides that just tried to enjoy the december with some filled lebkuchen, a couple clementines and M&amp;M&#x2019;s (the chocolates;) which I got in &#x2018;adventsgave&#x2019; - thanks mom... even though I&#x2019;m getting to old for this, it&#x2019;s still nice to get a present now and then. &#xD;Think that was it for this time. I will for sure have some news (though mostly work related) from Oxford. Luckily it will not all be work. Joakim, one of my friends from my studies in Copenhagen, has got a position in the ELIXIR collaboration as well (in Lyon) so it&#x2019;s gonna be nice to see him again - don&#x2019;t think I have seen him since I left DK. And then one of my high-school mates who is educating himself as racing engineer lives in Oxford, so I&#x2019;m hooking up with him saturday, which is for sure also gonna be great.&#xD;&#xD;But &#x2018;till then - take care!&#xD;/K</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Sunday, 6 December 2009&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
