<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20121225" date="2012-12-26 03:44:22 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;... 4 months late(r) ...&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Best-of winter &#x2019;11</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Cheers people&#xD;&#xD;I don't know why but it seems that most of my entries the last year or so starts with an apology for not having written anything for several weeks... well this time I think the apology is needed more than ever. As always I don't really have a valid excuse, but have just been busy and haven't really found the time (yeah okay It doesn't take that long to put together 100 lines of thoughts, but still) to biog. Well with the comin' of the spring I'm back online. I realize that last time I wrote in here was in the beginning of December... last year... ouch! So either a create a best-off the last 4 month entry, or I spend &#xA0;several hours giving you all the details of my "extremely interesting" life. Well the fact is that my life haven't been all that interesting the last couple of months and I then I'm too lazy to actually write about everything in here (as you have probably realize taking my frequency of entries into account), so a best-off it is.&#xD;&#xD;So where do I start? Well in December we threw quite some parties; just to celebrate life and christmas. Nothing spectacular happened at the parties (sorry Dolly, but I has been done before) just good atmosphere, lot's of booze; until we run out that is; and good company. Just before I went back to DK for Xmas we were a couple of guys who went to Stuttgart to watch a europa league match, which in end turned out to be a football lecture for OB - unfortunately; but it was a great night either way due to the awesome christmas market in Stuttgart - you still have something to learn here Heidelberg. I've put some pictures &lt;a href="http://gallery.me.com/kasperschmidt#100267&amp;view=null&amp;bgcolor=black&amp;sel=54"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; in case you haven't seen them already.&#xD;&#xD;When I got back to DK for Xmas I ended up putting my life completely on stand-by, by witch I mean I relaxed as I haven't relaxed in a long time. Christmas was luckily not that hectic this year. I was spending christmas eve at my parents, just us, my brother and my grandma. New years eve I spend with Mette and in between I only had a couple of julefrokoster which gave me plenty of time just to sit back and relax. On top of that end of December was REALLY snowy in DK, meaning that everyone sort of relaxed even more, and enjoyed the vacation instead of stressing around. Actually my dad and I almost got stuck when we drove to Mette's parents place on christmas day to exchange gifts... and that was about all the holiday 'action' I got, which suited me quite well.&#xD;&#xD;After christmas I went back to germany and had like 6 weeks of working before Mette visited in mid February. During the winter we talked about getting together for a 'social' event in my office. This ended up in a poker night at my place in the end of February. This turned out to be one of the best nights I have had in a long time, which might have something to do with the fact that I beat the crap out of the rest of the guys - better luck next time team india, MC and MG! I think the best way to describe the night is not to write anything but simply just recommend you to check out the pics :)&#xD;&#xD;In the beginning of march I had a meeting in Leiden, the Netherlands, which was meant to last for a couple of days. However, we needed to sort out some things, which suddenly gave me a Saturday of roaming around in Amsterdam. In the beginning I was kind of disappointed about the tourist-mayhem which Amsterdam seems to be, but as the hours went by and I managed to get away from the main pedestrian shopping street, the red light district and the coffee-shops I ended up actually liking Amsterdam. It reminded me quite a bit about Copenhagen, which I really miss down here. Of course tourists, red light district and coffee-shops is part of why Amsterdam is Amsterdam, so it's not that I think they should not be there, it's just that too much is too much. Well in the end it was a great trip, but I was also happy to get back to the hotel in Leiden in the evening... I was completely devastated after 8-10 hours of roaming around A'dam.&#xD;&#xD;Since I cam back I have been trying to get up to speed/date with my work since april is gonna be pretty busy with visitors. Last week the old folks were here. The weather was great and I really enjoyed a weekend just chillin' in the sun and enjoying life. Next week Mette and her family is coming by for a guided weekend in Heidelberg so I just hope that the weather will be as great as last (and this) weekend when they are here, and over easter my brother will make Heidelberg the honors, so that's gonna be great as well.&#xD;&#xD;Before I finish off and close down (hopefully not for 4 months again) I just want to point everyones attention to a blog that I have been following via facebook the last several months. &lt;a href="http://creolbrothers.cover.dk"&gt;The Creol Brothers&lt;/a&gt; put together a collection of the best stuff the internet, music and fashion offers. Check it out it is AWESOME!!!&#xD;&#xD;'til next time&#xD;KBS&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Sunday, 10 April 2011&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="10_Best-of_winter_11_files/shapeimage_2.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="360px" height="386px"/>
</content>
