<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160306" date="2016-03-06 10:02:39 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Motivation Please&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Master of Procrastination</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>As I wrote last time the date of handing in my thesis is quickly approaching. Unfortunately the thesis is not writing itself meaning that I actually have to do it. And when you are/have become a master of procrastination it's sometimes really hard to make the fingers dance on the keyboard producing wise and enlightening science *blah blah*. Today I planned to take a first stab a the scientific introduction but ended up doing loads of other things - the motivation and drive was kind of missing. Not really a sin as long as it doesn't happen every day/weekend but still...&#xD;&#xD;Besides getting most of the scientific pieces together for the thesis put together last week I was almost broad to my knees by a cold. Not really so tough that I was completely unable to work but enough that I felt sorry for myself while emptying package after package of paper towels. However, taking into account that I haven't really been ill for the last... what? 5 years or so, I think I got around it pretty easy this time. Hope this was a one-timer - knock on wood!&#xD;&#xD;Well, that was enough complaining for this time. One of the things I spent my day doing, now that I wasn't working as much as planned, was going vinyl-hunting with MG. For his birthday last year we gave him a record player which he recently got his pre-amplifier for such that it is now working. He therefore wanted to buy some new old records and since I was looking for an excuse to get out a bit, record-store-roaming and lunch was exactly the offer I needed. There are two vinyl places in HD. I knew about them but never really went through the records, since I don't have a record player myself. I always wanted to start collecting vinyls instead of (or rather: as well as) CDs - the vinyl is kinda the king/mother of CDs - but never really made the turn. However, flipping through the records with MG today reminded me why I collect... and why it would be so awesome to have a collection of vinyls as well. And I must admit; the two vinyl-pushers were really well equipped. You could really tell that records are getting a revival. They had some old school drum'n'bass, some Kraftwerk, a bit of new danish(!) records, e.g., Bon Homme and Kasper Bj&#xF8;rke, and they even had the new Modeselektor album which I didn't expect at all - I don't even think they have the CD version in Saturn... But not only did they have some new great electronic releases on vinyl, all the second hand records are simply amazing to flip through... I should really get me that turntable so it would make sense to buy vinyl! &#xD;&#xD;After finding some cool records for MG (even though he wasn't crazy about my recommendations - except maybe the Kraftwerk records) we went to MoschMosch noodle house to get some lunch. Mette and I have passed it several times saying "we should do that" but never really got around to do it. But we should have done it a long time ago 'cause it was really great - fried noodles with fresh vegetables, chili marinated beef and homemade ice tea was exactly what I needed. Definitely recommendable.&#xD;&#xD;Oh - btw. Speaking of the new Modeselektor album (also recommendable; pre-ordered the CD as soon as I realized it was on its way and there are some really neat tracks on there!) MG and I are going to their concert in Halle02 in two weeks. While I was in the US I saw that they were passing buy HD and after a great gig when I heard them in Copenhagen I bought the ticket right away. I managed to convince MG to buy one as well so at least I'm not going there alone. But if anyone want's to join just buy the ticket online and show up or drop either MG or me a line - it's gonna be so sweet; they know how throw a party!&#xD;&#xD;- Till next time -&#xD;KBS</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Saturday, 10 March 2012&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
