<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20121225" date="2012-12-26 03:44:21 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Busy Bee, That is Me... How Poetic :/&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Getting Ready for Heavy Traveling!</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Back in Heidelberg after my cousins &#x2018;confirmation&#x2019; and from a week of work from Denmark. I left Germany early saturday morning. I didn&#x2019;t concider that it was feiertag on 1st of may, which meant that the trams didn&#x2019;t really fit into my schedule so in order to catch my Lufthansa shuttle I had to walk into the city center (I&#x2019;m too cheap to take a cab;), meaning that I had to get up at 5. But the weather was great so I didn&#x2019;t mind. When I got to DK Mette was waiting in the airport which was a really present surprise :D She was a bit hungover since she visited a friend of hers the evening before, so she took a nap in the train to Funen. Around an hour after we got to Odense my parents came by to pick us up, since we were going to the &#x2018;confirmation&#x2019; of my cousin which was a 3 hours drive from Odense, so when we finally arrived in &#x2018;the dark Jutland&#x2019; I was kinda tired - it was a long day - so takeaway was a pretty good way to finish off the day. The whole sunday we didn&#x2019;t do anything except eating and drinking... which is not bad. It was nice to see the whole family again and to spend some hours catching up with my cousins. Monday morning we left for Funen after a good breakfast (yeah you know I like that as well ;)&#xD;The rest of the week in DK I spent working and just enjoying being around Mette. Thursday night her parents came by since they had invited us to the circus, which was in town. The main reason was probably that I&#x2019;ve told Mette that I&#x2019;ve never been to the circus, and since she went there several times as a  kid, Mette (and her parents I guess:) consider the fact that I&#x2019;ve never been to the circus as a flaw in my upbringing. So the wanted to make that right. Before we went to the circus we had them for dinner, where we made some awesome burgers... yes it seems that this blog is all about food.&#xD;The circus was pretty cool. A couple of the &#x2018;numbers&#x2019; (is it called like that?) were pretty dull but there were also a couple of amazing artists in between. And the clowns also made me laugh several times, so it was a success! &#xD;Saturday Mette and I went out for early dinner before I drove to Copenhagen, to spend the night at Martin&#x2019;s place (had an early sunday flight so it&#x2019;s much more convenient this way). Martin had invited a couple of guys over for a beer but because of the early flight I unfortunately was not able to join them as they moved. Next time!&#xD;I got safely back to Heidelberg (even though the volcano was threatening to mess things up) with a huge smile on my face - Denmark had beat Finland with 4-1 at the ice hockey world cup the night before. GO DANES! Monday they then played against the US and also beat them! So luckily it didn&#x2019;t matter that they lost to Germany yesterday - they are still through to the middle round!&#xD;Speaking about ice hockey... I don&#x2019;t know if I already mentioned it we bought ticket for a couple of matches this saturday - it&#x2019;s gonna be AWESOME!!&#xD;After ice hockey (and beers I guess;) this weekend my &#x2018;travel season&#x2019; this year takes off. From now on until the end of june I&#x2019;m only in Heidelberg around 14 days... so it&#x2019;s gonna be tough - and exciting. Therefore I&#x2019;m not really sure when the next blog entry will be, but I&#x2019;ll try to upload pictures at often as possible, so keep yourself updated &lt;a href="http://gallery.me.com/kasperschmidt"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; if you are curious.&#xD;&#xD;Cheers&#xD;/K</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Thursday, 13 May 2010&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="13_Getting_Ready_for_Heavy_Traveling%21_files/shapeimage_2.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="439px" height="348px"/>
</content>
