<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160306" date="2016-03-06 10:02:44 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Thanks IKEA and Walmart&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Furnished place - yes sir!</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>So a couple of weeks flew by again. As I&#x2019;m writing this I&#x2019;m somewhere over the east coast on my way back from the Netherlands where we held the last ELIXIR meeting monday and tuesday. But more about that below, as I have to give my probs to IKEA and Walmart first.&#xD;&#xD;As I mentioned last time we ordered a whole bunch of stuff from IKEA and a couch from Walmart and last week everything got delivered. It&#x2019;s incredible how much you appreciates a damn couch and a dining table when you have lived with only a bed, chairs and a small table for almost 2 months. We spent a couple of days getting everything put together (it is kind of a puzzle when you have larger furniture from IKEA) and only one small thing was missing. Luckily it was nothing important (a &#x2018;lock&#x2019; for the dinner-table-extensions) so I must say that I&#x2019;m grateful to both IKEA and Walmart for being so corporative... well IKEA didn&#x2019;t really do much except for handing over the goods to their carrier. But nevertheless, it&#x2019;s great to have a furnished place :) Therefore it won&#x2019;t be long before I post some pictures; but in case you haven&#x2019;t realized I&#x2019;m trying to upload real-time updates on Instagram (usr: kabosc) and FB.&#xD;&#xD;Last week was not only exciting because of the furniture delivery. It was also the week where I got a crash-course in the new projects I&#x2019;m gonna work on the next years. I already knew kind of what it was about (spectroscopic confirmation of redshift 8 galaxy candidates from the &lt;a href="https://wolf359.colorado.edu"&gt;BoRG survey&lt;/a&gt;), but last week L. Bradley and M. Trenti (he&#x2019;s actually also here this week) passed by UCSB to get me up to speed on the project(s). There was A LOT of information to absorb and frustration with some of the code, but in the big picture it was extremely useful to have both of them hanging around and burying me in info on the project. As this was really useful it was also a pity that I had to &#x2018;run off&#x2019; to Leiden last saturday, but this had been planned for quite some time.&#xD;&#xD;The reason I had to fly to Leiden, was as mentioned, that we had the last ELIXIR meeting (the Marie Curie network I was payed by during most of my time in Heidelberg). This also means that I haven&#x2019;t fully enjoyed the furnished place yet... but I&#x2019;ll have plenty of time to do that when I get back tonight :)&#xD;Well; even though the timing of the meeting was rather inconvenient it was great to see all the &#x2018;usual suspects&#x2019; again. &#xD;The meeting program was rather short so there was plenty time to be social - which was only fair as this was the last meeting of the network. To finish the whole thing of we (all the students) went out for one last lunch yesterday before a bunch of us took the train to Amsterdam. No tears but still kind of weird that none of us have any clue when and where we&#x2019;ll meet again. In Amsterdam I had time to pass by &lt;a href="http://www.iamsterdam.com/en-GB/Ndtrc/Concerto"&gt;Concerto&lt;/a&gt; - probably the best record store I have been to - for the third time ;) Some people go to Amsterdam to get high on weed or women; I get high on music there!&#xD;Before the actual program started monday and tuesday I spend sunday with JR and his boys. A very grown-up but awesome day!! We managed to get the boys away from the tv and biked with them to a nearby playground (it was not raining - we even saw the sun!). After that we went grocery shopping in the most kids-friendly supermarket I have ever been to. They had singing cows and pigs to entertain the kids, shopping carts formed as F1 racers, bouncing castle and slides - pretty neat place. In the evening it was &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/St._Martin's_Day"&gt;St. Martin&#x2019;s day&lt;/a&gt;. This means that dutch kids go &#x2018;trick-or-treat&#x2019;. They are not dressed up as for halloween but carry small lanterns and sing songs for the people who open. We met with a bunch of other parents from the neighborhood, who seemed to have been coordinating this evening for a while. At 1800 hours hell broke loose. From basically all houses small kids with lanterns ran to the street in a quest for filling their bags with candy. Even JR didn&#x2019;t realize that so many kids lived in their neighborhood. It lasted for about an hour and the boys seemed pretty satisfied with their &#x2018;candy-catch&#x2019;. We went back to JR&#x2019;s place cooked some dinner which JR had to force the boys to eat before they dived into their catch of the night.&#xD;Before sunday I wasn&#x2019;t sure if the &#x2018;sugar-rush&#x2019; term was invented by parents to prevent kids from having too much candy, or if it was actually real... now I&#x2019;m not in doubt any more. The energy level of the boys exploded; they were chasing one another, eating candy, breakdancing, eating candy, shouting, eating candy, laughing, eating candy, fighting, eating candy, singing, and eating even more candy until they looked like they were over-dozing and went into something looking like a trance or coma of some kind. Pretty neat :) JR even said monday morning that his kids were hungover when they woke up. So &#x2018;sugar-rush&#x2019; is definitely real. Thanks for a great day mate!&#xD;&#xD;Well; think that&#x2019;s it for now. I think I&#x2019;ll manage to watch a last movie before we land in Houston and I have to find my flight to L.A. Am really looking forward to get home. 6 flights (adding up to ~25 hours in the air) in just 5 days is a bit too much. But after all it was worth it.&#xD;&#xD;Cheers,&#xD;Kasper&#xD;&#xD;Oh by the way - check out what Mette and I found in SEARS the other day... I think we know where to get our plastic christmas tree for this year - not!&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Wednesday, 14 November 2012&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="14_Furnished_place_-_yes_sir%21_files/shapeimage_6.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="537px" height="287px"/>
</content>
