<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160306" date="2016-03-06 10:02:36 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;workin&#x2019;?    |IIIII|     chillin&#x2019;?&#xD;&#xB4;oo`&#xD;~&#xD;(|_:_|)&#xD;|_||_|&#xD;||  ||&#xD;oo0 0oo&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Autumn spring - what&#x2019;s that about?</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Hi guys... &#xD;Back again from a short visit to DK. Didn&#x2019;t really do much - worked a bit and just spend time with Mette. Of course I also dropped by my parents place for lunch - I really miss proper rugbr&#xF8;d and danish toppings like leverpostej, frikadeller, rullep&#xF8;lse and smoked mackerel  - thanks mom :) As you might guess I&#x2019;m hungry... the potatoes are in the owen and the smell doesn&#x2019;t really help on my hunger - but then I thought that I could blog a bit while the dinner is finishing. So here I am, blogging about nothing and everything. But as mentioned I was in Denmark for a short visit last weekend. Besides Mette and my parents I also found the time to drop by my brother before I flew back monday morning. My brother, his girlfriend (which I met for the first time - nice girl...) just chilled to the tv, ordered some sushi and had a couple of games of &lt;a href="http://www.enigmadistribution.com/default.asp?moduleStep=1&amp;vareID=2050&amp;frontNav=0&amp;frontID=9&amp;frontModuleType=14&amp;returnModule=container&amp;returnLinkTable=3&amp;returnLinkID=25"&gt;Klickado&lt;/a&gt; which is actually a small funny &#x2018;inverse mikado&#x2019; game - especially because you suck at it Martin and Annkatrine :D Victory is sweet :p&#xD;Since I got back to Germany monday I have been working on H&#x3B1; velocity mapping of &lt;a href="http://apod.nasa.gov/apod/ap081022.html"&gt;NGC7331&lt;/a&gt; to get started on another part of my PhD project.&#xD;Yesterday I went out with M&amp;M to celebrate Dr. Rodon which was a pleasant way to end a dark and rainy week in Heidelberg... speaking about the whether - they said in the news the other day that tuesday it will be around 19 degrees in Baden-W&#xFC;rttemberg... wtf is that about? its mid november and the all-mighty gives us spring temperatures - well no need to complain - me like!&#xD;BibBibBib said the oven, meaning my dinner is (almost) ready. Talk (or write) to you soon.&#xD;&#xD;Ciao Bella&#xD;/K&#xD; &#xD;Btw. it seems that the comment feature is not really working... or are you just to lacy to give any comments on my entries? ;)</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Sunday, 15 November 2009&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
