<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160306" date="2016-03-06 10:02:36 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;HedKandi... not bad;)&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Autumn = spa&#xDF; with my Bro!</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Last weekend was one of the good ones. First of all my brother was visiting, and secondly I allowed myself to make it a day longer so I could really have some &#x2018;quality time&#x2019; with Martin. We spend most of the time just hanging out, talking (which we haven&#x2019;t really had any occasions to the last 6-10 months), eating and drinking - exactly how a good weekend should be! Martin arrived thursday night where we just stayed home. Friday we cruised up and down Hauptstrasse before we went home, cooked and dressed up for the evening. We were going to a bar called SKYlounge and afterwards for some dancing at a HedKandi party. The view from the SKYlounge which is located at... was i 7th floor, was nice. Not as nice as when we had a cold beer on the terrace at the castle when we went there to party some weeks ago, but still nice enough that I REALLY enjoyed it - which might have been mostly the company. Most of the HD crew joined for cocktails and dancing at the HedKandi. The Party was really awesome! A DJ firing it max and a lot of party ready people always works on me:) After some ours there and with sore feet we went for some food and a cap.&#xD;Saturday we went to Mandy&#x2019;s diner to have a good burger. It&#x2019;s a fast food restaurant build in an old train wagon which supposedly serve some of the best (and biggest) burgers in Heidelberg. The location was really really really awesome - they have really managed to capture the american diner feeling! The burgers were not convincing. They were good it is not that but for some reason they are not using proper meet in their burgers in Heidelberg. And the beef is really what makes a burger, and when it made of processed meet you can only enjoy the first 100 grams... which a poor if you are in a mood for a 200g burger. Well the location was awesome and we had a nice time so screw that Heidelberg haven&#x2019;t managed to top the danish burgers yet... wonder if they ever will?!&#xD;Saturday night we went to a PhD party and danced our asses of again (even though we started kinda slow with a good italian dinner and a cocktail in Unterestrasse). Sunday we simply just chilled until Martin got picked up by TLS in the evening.&#xD;THANKS FOR AN AWESOME WEEKEND BRO!&#xD;&#xD;Since last weekend I have been working full time since I wont be able to work that much next weekend. Next weekend I&#x2019;m in DK. Really looking forward to see Mette again... it&#x2019;s tough being apart, but then it&#x2019;s just even better to be together. So hard work this week and weekend and the coming week to I can recharge in DK with a good conscience next weekend.  &#xD;&#xD;So much for an update... think that&#x2019;s all I got this time.&#xD;Cheers&#xD;K</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Sunday, 1 November 2009&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="1_Autumn_%3D_spa_with_my_Bro%21_files/shapeimage_2.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="400px" height="300px"/>
</content>
