<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160306" date="2016-03-06 10:02:35 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;BBQ and spring - me like!!&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Oktoberfest in April ;)</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Since last time I blogged I have mostly been working - wie immer ;) However I have also been to Fr&#xFC;ehlingsfest in Stuttgart and had the first (couple) of BBQs this year which has been made possible by a excellent German spring with lots of sunshine and 25 degrees and very warm winds! Last week we had no seminar thursday night as usual so I suggested that we should have a BBQ which people were 100p up for. We therefore bought a official IMPRS08 grill and some coal and went to Neckarwiese, were the asian army managed to assemble the BBQ and light the fire after which the German &#x2018;blower&#x2019; Roman took over... when the BBQ was ready our Italian food mama took over and we had some bratwurst, chiwaptiti (or whatever the balkan meet thingies are called) and some pork. Before dinner Mario and I played a bit with a football in the warm setting sun... so yes it was indeed the stereotype-BBQ we were having.&#xD;Last Saturday we then went to Stuttgart to celebrate the coming of the spring with beer and roller coasters. We left around noon from Heidelberg Hbf. The train ride was about 1.5 hours and went smoothly. Mario and I had quite some fun listening to German drunk football fans &#x201C;singing&#x201D;, since we were sharing the train with Eintracht and VfB fans going to Stuttgart for the last saturdays match.&#xD;When we cam to Stuttgart we spend a couple of hours walking up and down K&#xF6;nigstrasse, which is the main shopping street in Stuttgart, and had a couple of drinks on an artificial &#x2018;sky-beach&#x2018; on top of Kaufhof, which was really really really awesome!!&#xD;When the evening approached we took the s-bahn to the Fr&#xFC;ehlingsfest. Here we tried a couple of their &#x2018;carousels&#x2018; and roller coasters before we found a nice place to have some German dirndls... I mean beers.&#xD; Unfortunately we had to leave quite early (~2130) to catch the last train back to Heidelberg, but we then decided to go to Halle02 when we got back to HD... so yes we managed to get ourselves drunk... :)&#xD;&#xD;This weekend I have mostly been working, but we had another BBQ thursday at Marios place and went out for cocktails friday... just to get a bit out. Yesterday we went to see the lightening of the new lights on the old bridge. It was not really what they have tried to make i to... yes there is light on the bridge - but nothing really spectacular. We therefore decided to have some beers in memory of the old lights on the old bridge.&#xD;&#xD;And then... I would like to introduce a new &lt;a href="perma://BLPageReference/0E4DCFE0-6087-4808-908C-A98C45659677"&gt;concept on my website...&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Sunday, 3 May 2009&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="3_Oktoberfest_in_April_%3B%29_files/shapeimage_3.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="417px" height="313px"/>
</content>
