<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160306" date="2016-03-06 10:02:31 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>The danish tourist</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Well, another week gone... mostly working but still enjoying myself in &#x2018;sunny&#x2019; california. The weather have been sort of  okay even though it has been raining quite a bit, the wind is kind of cold and the &#x2018;natives&#x2019; say that I chose the worst week to come. But 20 degrees in the sun and 70% sunshine is way better than snow and cold in Germany. Actually they say that it has been snowing like hell in Heidelberg the last week ... wait a second - can it snow in hell? Well I guess you get the point.&#xD;As I said most of the week Phil and I have been working hard to get the most out of the time we are together, therefore a lot of hours have been spend indoors in front of my laptop. But luckily there have been time to socialize a bit in the evenings. Tuesday we went to a dinner party at Phil&#x2019;s girlfriends house, where her and her roommates had made some cherizo-thing wrapped in bacon, which was really good. We sad around their dining table, enjoying the food, drinking some beers and had several good laughs. &#xD;Wednesday I joined Phil&#x2019;s soccer team for a couple of hours of training. Unfortunately Phil was ill so he didn&#x2019;t join - maybe next wednesday... I borrowed a pair of football shoes  from Phil and gave it all I got. Thursday and friday a was reminded that it has been a long time since I have played soccer regularly - I was sour in ALL of my body - but it was still worth it, and if my blisters are all right wednesday I&#x2019;ll join them again. Friday night we went out for burgers at Paradise Caf&#xE9;. Phil had lost a bet to his boss so he owed him a couple burgers, which I then joined in on. The burgers were good but the fries were horrible - but I guess the burger is the important part here! We had a coupe of red stripes (a jamaican beer which is quite) before we went home early after a long weeks work were we definitely &#x2018;earned our beers&#x2019;. &#xD;Yesterday I went to a farmers marked downtown Santa Barbara were I tasted the best orange I&#x2019;ve ever got (I think). At noon I teamed up with Phil and helped a couple of friends of his moving in to their new house in SB. When we had emptied their moving truck, Phil, Emily and I drove north so I could take a dive in the pacific and finally get my shorts wet. It was cold but not that cold; I am after all a viking from the north... sort of;) After my dive and Phil&#x2019;s nab we drove Solvang for tea and danish pastry. &lt;a href="http://www.solvangusa.com/"&gt;Solvang&lt;/a&gt; is a REALLY &#x2018;tacky&#x2019; danish-immigrants-not-beeing-able-to-let-go-of-denmark town in eastern california. We had some danish pastry at Mortensen&#x2019;s bakery were they had decorated with posters from &#xC6;r&#xF8; and posters of queen Magrethe and her husband - really weird but kind of funny to. When we came back to Santa Barbara we went out for beers and steaks with the guys we helped move in.&#xD;Today I have taken it really slow. Went to &#x2018;the Mission&#x2019; (an old monastery from the 1780s) and did a bit of shopping on State st. Before I went back to the hotel I had a sandwich at the beach enjoying the sun - I don&#x2019;t think I would have a problem living here.&#xD;Since I came back to the hotel this afternoon I have just been chillin&#x2019; to some telly. Tomorrow the work will continue until thursday where Phil and I will drive to Tucson, AZ which is gonna be really cool. US and road-trips just go great together;)&#xD;Thanks for your comments on my last entry - keep &#x2018;em coming.&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;EARN YOUR BEERS!</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Monday, 16 February 2009&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="16_The_danish_tourist_files/shapeimage_2.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="400px" height="300px"/>
</content>
