<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160306" date="2016-03-06 10:02:31 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Almost ready for the US</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>After another harsh weekend with a bit of work and some alkohol (read nasty vodka-party) I&#x2019;m almost ready to leave for the US on saturday.&#xD;Today I have not done much except regenerating after yesterday. We were a couple of us who went for a vodka party in Neuenheimer Feld. The idea was that everybody should bring a bottle of vodka and then the hosts made sure that there were enough to mix with - and so there were indeed. Everything from pickles to &#x2018;sparkling powder candy&#x2019; and juice in all colors. I was home kind of late so slept until lunch today. When I got up I started to pack my suitcase for the US trip. It seems that there is sort of enough space in my suitcase (I hope). I was a bit worried that stuff for a month overseas couldn&#x2019;t fit in my suitcase - but I don&#x2019;t think it will be a problem. The problem might be bringing back all of the souvenirs... if I buy any... but no need to worry about that now.&#xD;Then I also saw the handball world championship bronze mach between Denmark and Poland - and sorry for my language - but what a fucking bunch of shit! It&#x2019;s hard to admit, but Denmark deserved to loose! Come on guys... step up!&#xD;Well besides that I haven&#x2019;t done much today. Just mentally preparing for the US. I still have to make the talk they asked me to give as a &#x2018;payment&#x2019; for their official invitation. Hope the talk will be good:)&#xD;The next five days will be filled with work so I&#x2019;m ready to leave saturday where I have to take the tram already at 0620 a.m. in order to catch the right train to Frankfurt airport,. My plain for L.A. is scheduled to leave at around 0945 a.m. and after ~11 hours in the air I will be in Gods own country at 1230 a.m. pacific standard time. It&#x2019;s gonna be good to switch from &#x2018;cold-wet-dark-Heidelberg&#x2019;-mode to (hopefully) &#x2018;sunny-hot-crazy-California&#x2019;-mode in less than one week... I&#x2019;m for sure looking forward to it.&#xD;Btw. since I have moved the website to this server you can now subscribe via an rss feed to my blog so you will know when a post a new entry. And since it is MUCH easier to publish my entries and changes to thus server, I hope and think that I will have time to blog a bit more than usual when I&#x2019;m &#x2018;over there&#x2019; the next month or so... and of course ... as I have already mentioned on the main page, you are more than welcome to use the new &#x2018;comment&#x2019; function in the blog section (se bottom of this page;).&#xD;Well I think this was it for this time... hope to hear from you all.&#xD;&#xD;Cheers - and fingers crossed that my trip will be smooth&#xD;Kasper</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Sunday, 1 February 2009&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="1_Almost_ready_for_the_US_files/shapeimage_4.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="453px" height="270px"/>
</content>
