<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20130128" date="2013-01-28 17:22:48 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;New Year - New Location&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Exposing......</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Happy new year everyone and belated happy Xmas. While we are collecting photons and the data from yesterday is being reduced I have some time to kill so thought I would say high as I didn&#x2019;t manage to over christmas. However, first of all let me take the opportunity to point everyone to the fact that I moved my website and blog to a new location at the UCSB server last week. So if you are a regular visitor (or want to become one) make sure you update your bookmarks accordingly. The main page can now be found at &lt;a href="http://www.physics.ucsb.edu/~kschmidt/"&gt;www.physics.ucsb.edu/~kschmidt/&lt;/a&gt;. &#xD;As always December just got started before it was over. Most of the time I spent preparing observations with MOSFIRE on &lt;a href="http://keckobservatory.org"&gt;Keck&lt;/a&gt;. Yesterday night and now (exposing as I write ;) When I was not working Mette and I were trying to wrap our heads about celebrating christmas in sunny California. Luckily, this year December was apparently above-average grey, wet and chilly so the transition from a cold and wet danish/german December wasn&#x2019;t extreme. Nevertheless, it has been pretty weird with days of no need for a jacket in December - but as most other things over here we are slowly getting used to them. &#xD;Initially we were afraid not to get in the right christmas spirit this year but thanks to the overwhelming amount of christmas cards and gifts people send over here we managed to get in the right mood for the holidays. Before we knew we would get so many greetings from back home we tried to care of the mood ourselves, by going to the &#x2018;Parades of Lights&#x2019; festival (a parade of boats &#x2018;dressed&#x2019; in christmas lights) in the harbor where Santa was listening to kids&#x2019; wishes and to see the Nutcracker in one of the theaters on State St. Both events were pretty cool and also helped reminding us that it was about to be christmas.&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;On christmas eve we went out for dinner after having spent most of the day Skyping with people back home (It was pretty convenient that we could chime in at european evening-time and then had the rest of the day to ourselves), and after a long walk on the beach and a short dive in the Pacific; well for me that is.&#xD;The rest of the christmas vacation we spent mostly relaxing and enjoying life here in SB.&#xD;New years eve 2012 was very different in many ways. One thing is that we are here... another the fact that we had been awarded time with MOSFIRE on the night between December 31st and January 1st as well as the night between January 1st and 2nd (now). As it was new years eve Mette decided to join me in the remote observing room at the University for the whole night. At midnight we went to the 6th floor where there is a great view towards the city to see the fireworks. We had noticed that nothing was going on in the days before the 31st - it was not like in DK where people test their fireworks well in advance of new years eve - so we were curious to see if people actually had anything for new years eve... and they didn&#x2019;t!! We were outside looking towards the city from 23:55 to 0010 and we saw 1; yes ONE rocket?!?! That&#x2019;s just crazy (and extremely disappointing). The only semi-sane explanation we can come up with is that it must be illegal to handle fireworks without a permit... but at least the city could then have put something together. But no - there was nothing at all. Hence, new years eve turned pretty quiet this year - maybe we&#x2019;ll take revenge when going into 2014.&#xD;Think that was it for this time. The next couple of weeks will be busy; Mette&#x2019;s sister and cousin are flying in on Saturday after a stop in San Francisco. It&#x2019;s gonna be pretty neat to have them here and to experience a bit of the country side with them.&#xD;&#xD;Till next time&#xD;K&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Wednesday, 2 January 2013&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="2_Exposing......_files/shapeimage_2.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="500px" height="316px"/>
</content>
