<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160306" date="2016-03-06 10:02:30 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Moving - nice!</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>AT LAST - I&#x2019;ve got my own place. This thursday (October 30) I moved into my new flat in the southern part of Heidelberg. Luckily I was able to move in a couple of days before the first of november, so that I didn&#x2019;t have to spend two nights in Heidelberg without a place to sleep (read &#x2018;had to sleep two nights at the institute&#x2019;). Being able to move in by the 30th, however cost me a paint job. Usually it&#x2019;s the person moving out who has to paint the apartment (if it need to) but the guy who lived here before me said that he didn&#x2019;t have time to paint if he should be out already on the 30th - yeah right... he probably had plenty of time but saw an opportunity not to repaint the apartment, &#x2018;cause it REALLY need a paint job, as the pictures clearly show. Don&#x2019;t now when, but I WILL get the time (and money) to paint - I prefer white walls compared to the post-modern-crack-crap-mixed-spunge-colored-walls that are here now! Well I moved in thursday at 10 a.m. I didn&#x2019;t have that much stuff to move - mostly close - so the apartment was really empty thursday. Actually i found myself thursday evening alone one my air madras, with a pizza in one hand and a beer in the other in a very dark apartment only lid by the light above the kitchen sink - kind of weird, but also quite funny;)&#xD;Well, this was only thursday, because friday my parents drove down here to visit me and see Heidelberg, and they brought some of my stuff so now I&#x2019;m on top! My parents arrived friday around 18 p.m. We emptied the car and went to Rewe after some beers. When we came back we enjoyed some danish black bread and just chilled. Saturday I wanted to show them the Hauptstrasse, the Castle, the old bridge etc. The Hauptstrasse was kind of easy and didn&#x2019;t take that long, since saturday was a public &#x2018;feiertag&#x2019; so all of the shops were closed (sorry mom;). This came as a surprise but just meant that we had more time to see the other stuff. &#xD;In the late afternoon we found a restaurant and had a real german dinner, i.e., beer, schnitsel, speatzel, etc. When we came back to the apartment we played a game of Carcasonne and had a couple of beers to sleep on - great way of spending the saturday.&#xD;My parents left earlier today, so now I&#x2019;m just chillin&#x2019; to some Mtv and fixing the final stuff in the apartment.&#xD;... I&#x2019;ll paint next week ... or ... we&#x2019;ll see! </richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Sunday, 2 November 2008&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
