<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160306" date="2016-03-06 10:02:30 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Work &amp; Gl&#xFC;hwein</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>I think this entry will be rather short - sorry. The reason is that the couple of weeks haven&#x2019;t been much more than working to catch up. The work is in general progressing slowly but steady. At the moment I&#x2019;m both working on some theoretical stuff as well as some data stuff. Both areas are interesting, but especially the data part brings new challenges and it can sometimes be really frustrating using 2 hours on something which should take like 10 min. But I guess this is part of still learning... Well it&#x2019;s interesting and I actually look forward to go to the institute in the mornings. And at the moment there is snow at the mountain so it&#x2019;s actually &#x2018;cozy&#x2019; to go there. &#xD;Besides working I&#x2019;ve have also been out with some of the IMPRS students a couple of nights. Unterstrasse really seems to a place where you can spend a lot of nights (and money) without getting tired of it (maybe of the alcohol). Besides that the traditional christmas market opened wednesday, so we of course had to go there and have some gl&#xFC;hwein (hot spiced vine, tastes a bit like cheap danish gl&#xF6;gg so actually not that bad;) and a couple of bratwursts. Actually an excellent way to spend a thursday night, or friday, saturday, sunday, monday, tuesday or wednesday night:)&#xD;Yesterday I went to Hauptstrasse to buy some cologne for my grandma&#x2019; - and that&#x2019;s the &#x2018;real&#x2019; one from Cologne: 4711. It&#x2019;s impossible to get in Denmark, so my parents asked me to bye some so we could give her a nice surprise for christmas - consider it done! Besides that I picked up the hardware for my internet connection at home. Thursday a guy from Telekom will (hopefully) come by and &#x2018;turn the web on&#x2019;. Even though I&#x2019;ve bought the connection from Vodafone, Telekom are still the only ones who can open the connection, and of course they cant do that by pushing a button; they have to send a gay which means that I have to be at home waiting thursday - hurray for German efficiency... But fingers crossed that it then works the second he turns it on. It&#x2019;s really frustrating not to have internet in my apartment yet so I have to do all the internet thingies at the institute - well I guess it&#x2019;s over by the end of next week - fingers crossed.&#xD;Hmmm guess that was it for this time. &#xD;Cheers, and happy &#x2018;most-stressful-month-in-year&#x2019;&#xD; &#xD;&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Sunday, 30 November 2008&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
