<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160306" date="2016-03-06 10:02:38 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Am I stressed or just hungover?&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Christmas ... already?!</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>I&#x2019;m dizzy... kind of not really hungry but on the same time hungry and my mouth is dry. It could be stress but today it&#x2019;s just because of yesterdays christmas party at Roman&#x2019;s place, and next saturday there is another one. Not that I have the time for it but it&#x2019;s hard to say no to a good party (and I won&#x2019;t). I just realized that it yet again has been quite a while since I blogged last time... I really have to do something about the frequency with which I write here.&#xD;Well, since it has been more than two months since last time quite a bit has happened. Even though I haven&#x2019;t been good at blogging I try to keep my &lt;a href="http://gallery.me.com/kasperschmidt"&gt;galleries&lt;/a&gt; up to date so you at least can follow along there - and since a picture says more than a thousand words, that&#x2019;s not a bad substitute for regular blogging I guess. But as mentioned a lot of stuff has happened. Mette has been here, I had a meeting in Paris and a workshop in Baltimore plus a trip to DK, so I haven&#x2019;t been bored.&#xD;When Mette was here we actually didn&#x2019;t do much... which was great. We just went for a couple of walks, to a look at the castle, went out for dinner with the HD-crew and besides that just enjoyed life. &#xD;A couple of weeks after Mette left I had a mid-term review of the ELIXIR collaboration (which pays my salary) to attend. The mid-term review was combined with a short two day meeting so in the end I had tuesday-saturday in Paris. The meeting itself was pretty relaxed and down to earth. Since I know more or less everyone in the collaboration now it was very informal (except for the review of course) and we basically just had a good time. We went out every night for good food and wine, as one should in Paris. One evening we went to an ethiopian restaurant. I also tried ethiopian in Yale in september and I think I&#x2019;m developing something for ethiopian food. We were pretty lucky with the weather, except for saturday where is was raining, so friday we actually just had wine, cheese, sweets and baguette at the banks of the Seine... that&#x2019;s life as it should be :) Another awesome thing about the meeting was the meeting dinner which was at &lt;a href="http://www.musee-orsay.fr/en/home.html"&gt;Mus&#xE9;e d&#x2019;Orsay&lt;/a&gt;. Before the dinner we had a ~2 hour long guided tour of the museum which was pretty cool. Unfortunately all the Monet was lent out to a large exhibition but there were plenty of other impressive paintings. I especially liked the &#x2018;pointism&#x2019; paintings - pretty cool and impressive when they get of a certain size. The food afterwards was not as good as one could expect; or to be more precise, the main dish wasn&#x2019;t convincing - the 3 other dishes though, were pretty great. The atmosphere in the restaurant was very special. Very tall ceilings (don&#x2019;t know if that&#x2019;s the correct way to put it but you get the idea) and golden chandeliers and large mirrors on the walls... kind of like in a baroque castle of some kind - it made us feel special ;)&#xD;When I got back from Paris a had a weeks time of work before I had to go to a small workshop in Baltimore. I left saturday and got back already the wednesday after, so it was a pretty short trip (the meeting was monday and tuesday) but I had some time to take a look around on the sunday - and the weather was AWESOME: more than 20C and sun. I went to Baltimore&#x2019;s inner harbor on the sunday which was pretty neat, especially in the great weather. I spent some hours just walking around and enjoying the warm autumn - too bad I didn&#x2019;t bring my better half. For lunch I went to a very cosy old neighborhood further out the harbor, bought a sandwich to-go and hung out on one of the piers. In the evening I met with one of my ELIXIR colleagues who was also in Baltimore for some dinner. We had a large burger and a cheesecake at the Cheesecake Factory. Pretty okay food, but I was disappointed that they were not wearing the same outfit as &lt;a href="http://www.cbs.com/primetime/big_bang_theory/"&gt;Penny in TBBT&lt;/a&gt;... wonder how much the Cheesecake Factory actually pays for having her working there - it&#x2019;s definitely good PR. Since I flew back already tuesday evening that was sort of the sight-seeing I managed to do there, and despite the reputation of Baltimore being the american city with the highest &#x2018;murder-rate&#x2019; (whatever that means) the city (center) was pretty cool.&#xD;As mentioned I got back wednesday. I landed in Frankfurt around noon, where I got a lift with my supervisor and his wife, who also came back to Germany from travels that day - I actually took the same connection from Heathrow as Mary-Beth. Already the saturday after I flew to DK to work from there for a week. However, I almost didn&#x2019;t make it. That week there was an increased security in most of germany because of terror threats. And since they apparently had stopped a train on the way to the airport, the tracks from Mannheim to the airport could not be used, and my train was led over Duisburg instead. That combined with the fact that the train didn&#x2019;t go to the airport all of a sudden, so I had to change to the subway at Frankfurt main station, meant that I was in the airport 35 minutes before my flight. I thought that the check-in time was 45 minutes before departure, so were pretty sure I missed it. Luckily it turns out that one can check in to Lufthansa&#x2019;s &#x2018;commuter&#x2019; flights 30 minutes before departure, so when I came running to the counter all sweaty, the girl behind it just smiled and said &#x201C;take it easy you still have 5 minutes&#x201D;... well it was pretty close, but I set a new record either way: Check-in-security-gate in Frankfurt: 8 minutes and came to Denmark as planned. The time in DK went by with work, relaxing, shopping and dinner at Mette&#x2019;s parent&#x2019;s place and dinner with my parents.&#xD;I came back from Denmark last sunday to a sunny and chilly weather but no snow as in DK (the week I was there we got quite a bit). It was only white at the mountain, but that changed this monday. Now everything is white down here as well. It however looks like it is going to change a bit next week where the temperatures should rise above 0 degrees. But the white landscape fitted the christmas/birthday party yesterday night pretty well - let&#x2019;s hope that it lasts until the 24th; or at least comes again so we will get a white christmas. But so far it looks good for DK.&#xD;Well - that&#x2019;s it for this time. Take care and enjoy December... I am - had my first couple of gl&#xFC;hweins and sausages last week at the christmas market, and have filled lebkuchen hearts and mandarins on the kitchen table, mmmm :)&#xD;&#xD;Cheers&#xD;Kasper&#xD;&#xD;ohh yeah btw. check out the date and time here ;)&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Sunday, 5 December 2010&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="5_Christmas_..._already%21_files/shapeimage_2.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="400px" height="300px"/>
</content>
