<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20121225" date="2012-12-26 03:44:12 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Conference &amp; HD continued</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Since last blog entry I have been rather busy. First of all I have found an apartment - sooo nice! It&#x2019;s located around 5 km. south of the central part of Heidelberg in the Rohrbach/Kirchheim area of Heidelberg. The apartment is about 30 square meters and because of that and its location rather cheap - which is great, since I still have to pay rent in DK; anyone who want to buy our apartment in Copenhagen (then go &lt;a href="http://www.nybolig.dk/maegler/PrivatBolig.jsp?sagsnr=03100623&amp;forretningsnr=104554"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;). So the living situation is sorted out - well more or less, I still have to be out of the guest house, where I&#x2019;m living at the moment the 30th and the apartment is available from the 1st. But I hope that I can move in a couple of days earlier - fingers crossed!!&#xD;Besides finding a new place to live, I have been working hard on getting and overview of the subjects I&#x2019;m about to get involved in at the Institute (which reminds me that I should update the &#x2018;interest&#x2019; in the science section ... well maybe next time!). As a part of my &#x2018;training&#x2019; I have been to a conference south of Munich last week, on the matters of classification and discovery in large astronomic surveys. The first day was kind of hard, since it was mostly computer guys giving talks, and most of the subjects (e.g. support vector machines, decision trees and (non)supervised machine learning) was therefore new to me. But as the workshop progressed, the subjects from monday made more and more sense, when combined with astrophysics of various kinds. In general the conference was really cool. It was held at Ringberg Castle, a middle-age-inspired castle build by a gay bavarian duke in the early/mid 1900s, which is now &lt;b&gt;the&lt;/b&gt; conference sight of the Max Planck Gesellschaft. Each day we had lunch and dinner at the castle, which was really &#x2018;best of&#x2019; the bavarian kitchen, meaning lots and lots of meat and beer - me like! Each night we hang out in the castle drinking, socializing and playing some table tennis.&#xD;Wednesday evening we went to a true bavarian restaurant down in Tegernsee. That was really a cool experience. One thing is that the large building in the small town Tegernsee is  a restaurant/bierstube, but that it&#x2019;s full (~200 people) with drunk germans and tourists on a wednesday night was amazing. We got a room for our selves, which was probably good, &#x2018;cause 60 drunk astrophysicists are not silent... we ate and drank until the bus came back for os and drove us home around 1030 p.m. I ordered &#x2018;schnapsw&#xFC;rtzl mit kartofeln/gurken salat und saurkrauth&#x2019; and with that &#x2018;Tegernseer Dunkel Bier aus fass&#x2019; - then it doesn&#x2019;t get any more bavarian, and it tasted great! (Un)fortunately the only bar in Kreuth (where 20 of the participants and I lived during the conference) was closed when we came back so I was not (that) hangover thursday. After a week of a lot of talks, bavarian food and beers I came back to Heidelberg with the train friday at around 7 p.m. Yesterday and today I have used most of the days to digest the (scientific) impressions from the conference, so that I&#x2019;m ready to get back to work monday morning.&#xD;Tuesday I&#x2019;m meeting with the estate agent of my new apartment, and he will by then hopefully tell me that I can move in a bit earlier, so that I will not have to sleep at the &#x2018;street&#x2019; from the 30th until November 1st.</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Saturday, 18 October 2008&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
