<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20121225" date="2012-12-26 03:44:12 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Enigma @ Greece 26-29th of September 08</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>As a small break in my new german life, I went to Greece with the guys (sorry Maiken) from my (old :&#x2019;( ) job. We went to the north-western part of Peloponnes near the REAL olympic stadium.  We arrived at the hotel rather late, and because of the long drive from the airport, and a short stop in Korinthos most of us were quite drunk when we arrived, so we just had a couple of beers an some pizza before we went to bed. The next day we drove to a wine yard - mostly because of the possibility to taste some local wine straight from the barrels. Afterwards we went to the olympic stadium. Here we ran the original famous &#x2018;stadium&#x2019; which corresponds to a straight distance of about 192 meters - unfortunately I didn&#x2019;t win:( Besides running at the olympic stadium we all got an excellent and outstanding historical presentation of the area around the stadium from our beloved &#x2018;chief&#x2019; Mr. Danger.&#xD;When we cam back to the hotel we played some poker and drank some more beers - how lovely...&#xD;Sunday was the day of the great mach, which has a tremendous effect on the daily life at Enigma the rest of the year. We were all ready and the mach got of with a good start. Unfortunately the danes were afraid of loosing so when Linus tied the game for the swedes, Martin, John and Peter broke his arm and the game was stopped. So much for fair play you silly danes... better luck next year guys!&#xD;Monday we had a 4 hours drive to the airport and flew tired and &#x2018;hangovered&#x2019; back to Copenhagen.&#xD;Thanks for a(nother) great trip!!&#xD;(there&#x2019;s a lot more pictures &lt;a href="perma://BLPageReference/860D7FC3-3597-4A2C-99DB-8FF963D27304"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;)</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Friday, 3 October 2008&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
