<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160306" date="2016-03-06 10:02:46 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Busy Bee&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Long time no see</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Time&#x2019;s flying. Haven&#x2019;t had the time to post here as life has been crazy busy here since Christmas. January started out with a remote observing run as I described last time. This meant that there was plenty to do at work. On top of that Mette&#x2019;s sister and cousin passed by in January for a couple of weeks. This meant a couple of days in San Francisco incl. Alcatraz, roadtrip down the pacific coast highway and death valley, as well as a short stop at Las Vegas and Hoover damn. All recommendable and pretty darn amazing :) The second week they were here was a bit more relaxed just chillin&#x2019; in SB, hiking and eating well.&#xD;After they left SB we had a couple of weeks before the next visit which we spent finding ourselves again. Then in the beginning of february Mette&#x2019;s parents came. It was there first major trip outside Europe so we were kind of nervous about them traveling here. But everything went fine, and even though the time difference and the long trip was tough on them they made it here without any problems (more than we can say about their return-flight were they had to run in SF to catch their connection to Europe - but luckily they did). Mette&#x2019;s parents were also here for 2 weeks. As opposed to when Mette&#x2019;s sister and cousin were here we spent most of the time in Santa Barbara. We drove to Solvang one day, went for a hike and spent a day in L.A. - well not really L.A. as we were on Venice Beach and IKEA Carson - but besides that we just enjoyed lovely SB. &#xD;Before Mette&#x2019;s parents arrived we managed to put the last of our things (mirrors, kitchen rack, pictures etc.) so all we needed to get 110% settled were some smaller things which we picked up in IKEA and getting our lamps up. Mette&#x2019;s dad helped with that (well actually he did everything himself - I got home from work one evening and they were up - sweet!) meaning that we are now fully functional with lamps, mirrors and everything. Great!!&#xD;H&amp;J left this tuesday, and despite a large delay from SB they got back to DK safe and sound.&#xD;Hubble proposals and Bayesian inference has taken most of my time this week so nothing crazy to report on that. This weekend will probably also be fairly work-heavy but the weather should be nice so I&#x2019;m pretty sure I will take a couple of hours in the sun in our new comfy-porch-chairs; we&#x2019;re livin&#x2019; in sunny Cali&#x2019; after all :)&#xD;&#xD;Cheers&#xD;KBS&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;Btw. Mette and I are flying to DK for a couple of weeks on March 23rd. So in case you are up for grabbing a coffee, dinner, cup of tea, lunch, beer, or whatever from the 24th onwards. Let us know...&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Saturday, 23 February 2013&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="22_Long_time_no_see_files/shapeimage_5.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="695px" height="224px"/>
</content>
