<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160306" date="2016-03-06 10:02:43 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Our Stuff Arrived&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Feeling more like home</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Friday our stuff arrived to Santa Barbara. We had teamed up with Mette&#x2019;s cousin who could fix a sweet deal for transporting a couple of pallets with FedEx. Surprisingly the FedEx freight option was by far the cheapest way to get our stuff from DK to SB compared to Post Danmark (no surprise here though), DHL, various container shippers, TNT, etc. We - or rather Mette and her parents - packed our things last friday so they could be picked up in DK this monday. FedEx were gonna fly it over here, so I could expect delivery already wednesday. I got the tracking number so I could keep an eye on the process myself but as I don&#x2019;t have internet at home yet, wednesday I was waiting &#x2018;blind&#x2019; and just keeping a close eye on my phone. Nothing happened. Hence, I passed by Starbucks half an hour before they closed wednesday night and checked the delivery status - and there seemed to be a problem. There was a &#x2018;clearance delay&#x2019; in Membhis. Luckily it turned out to be an easy fix. I called FedEx first thing thursday when I got to work and I simply had to sign a couple of forms as the receiver saying that I swear not to sell our stuff and that it was for personal use only. After that our pallets could be cleared in customs and friday around noon they arrived - pretty efficient I must say!&#xD;I unpacked everything right away meaning that now our new place actually starts looking like a home. And to make sure that any future visitors knows where we are from (one of) the flags in the shipment has gotten a prominent spot in the living room.&#xD;Besides now having a fully equipped kitchen so I can cook properly again (on the gas-stove which I&#x2019;m already falling in love with) we also got most of our electronics over here, including our tv. However, to be honest I&#x2019;m too cheap to pay 60 bucks a month for cable tv and I therefore think we will stick with whatever is broadcast the oldschool way. Until I buy a proper antenna tin foil and a bit of trial-an-error is plenty fine; well actually the lid of our new BBQ is great as antenna, so yesterday I was watching college football on abc - not bad at all. And I think abc will show some NBA when the season starts, so if we can then just catch some NBC when we get a proper antenna so we can watch some sunday NFL I&#x2019;m good. And if we want more &lt;a href="http://netflix.com"&gt;Netflix&lt;/a&gt; is definitely on the to-buy list together with an &lt;a href="http://www.apple.com/appletv/"&gt;Apple tv box&lt;/a&gt; (yeah I know... sorry). &#xD;Well - all this just to let you know that we now have a bit more furniture. Next step furniture wise is to get a dining table and a couch - but that can wait till Mette arrives.&#xD;&#xD;cheers&#xD;/K&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Monday, 24 September 2012&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="23_Feeling_more_like_home_files/shapeimage_4.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="441px" height="306px"/>
</content>
