<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160306" date="2016-03-06 10:02:37 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;(Belated) Happy Easter&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Back and going again...</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>What a GREAT easter... Got back wednesday and am up in working gear again. Before I left for easter I had a couple of things to finish though. As you might know I&#x2019;m arranging this monthly discussion session in Heidelberg on gravitational lensing. The idea is to gather the lensing community in HD and have a talk to start a scientific discussion revolving around lensing (to see a list of previous talks go &lt;a href="http://www.mpia.de/homes/kschmidt/LiHD.html"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;). Usually I don&#x2019;t have a problem finding a voluntary speaker but this month due to easter and proposal deadlines no-one signed up. Luckily I had reached a point in my research  where I could step in a give a lensing related talk. So far I haven&#x2019;t given a discussion starter myself because all my work have been on QSOs but we have recently started to move into &#x2018;lens-country&#x2019;. I therefore had to give a talk wednesday before I left for easter. In my own humble opinion the talk went well and the discussion/questions during and after the talk was good and constructive, so all i all a really good way to finish off before easter. I left for DK from HD around 6 o&#x2019;clock... and that&#x2019;s when the drama started! I left with the train towards Frankfurt airport as planned but unfortunately the train was delayed and I missed my check-in at the airport for the first time ever:( Due to the talk I couldn&#x2019;t take an earlier train so I only had a 20 min. buffer which unfortunately was not enough. It&#x2019;s not an excuse cause even when I am able to take an earlier tran I don&#x2019;t - so far I have trusted Deutsche Bahn blindly not to be more than max 15 minutes late on a 35 minutes trip... but I was wrong. Luckily the girl behind the counter could see the &#x2018;fear&#x2019; in my eyes when I told hear that I couldn&#x2019;t check in! I had already seen myself paying either 800&#x20AC; or talking a train back to HD, calling Mette and telling her that I wasn&#x2019;t coming after all - that would have been a NIGHTMARE. But as I said, she saw that I was desperate and luckily the plain was 10-15 minutes delayed because of heavy showers in Frankfurt, so I ran the best I&#x2019;ve learned (almost collapsed when I saw my gate on the boarding pass... A40 - you son of a b****!) but reached the gate even before people started boarding. So in the end everything worked out. I arrive at Mette&#x2019;s place around midnight and was more than prepared for 5 days of chillin&#x2019;!&#xD;We spent the easter eating and drinking with my parents, her parents and friends, so we were booked every day - but it was really nice spending some time with the family(x2) and especially Mette. Friday evening Mette and I went to the White Pony/Fagget Fairys I mentioned last time. And indeed it was an awesome concert - or at least the FF part. The DJset the threw as warm-up was GOD DAMN AMAZING - those girls rock big time! WP was also cool but unfortunately they didn&#x2019;t play that much from their own album (think they played like 4 of their own songs). They focused on throwing a huge party DJ&#x2019;ing instead, which would have been awesome if there were more than 40 people to the concert and if that was what Mette and I went there for. But since we went there for good live music and not a party-DJ-session the FF &#x201C;warm-up&#x201D; was the highlight of the night.&#xD;Besides that I didn&#x2019;t do much over easter - worked a tiny bit, but not really... Tuesday I went to Copenhagen where I spent the evening with my Bro. Before we crashed in front of the TV with some good food I dropped by my old spare time job at Enigma. Pretty nice to say high to the guys again. Wednesday morning I took a plane back to HD where I jumped right back into the work... I was actually enjoying getting back to work :)&#xD;Thus the rest of the week I&#x2019;ve just used tying up loose ends and getting back up to working-speed... oh and then we have started planning a birthday party next friday. Since Gisella and I both have our birthdays in April we have decided to throw a party together like last year. This time we are having it at my place, so if you are interested feel free to drop by my apartment on friday the 16th around 2100 hours and we&#x2019;ll be glad to offer you drinks and snacks!&#xD;But before partying I will have to work with the &#x2018;mantra&#x2019; Phil taught me in mind:&#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;&#x201C;Earn your beers!&#x201D;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;See you friday or talk to you soon!&#xD;/K&#xD;&#xD;B.t.w. Joining the party via Skype (video and/or sound) will be possible if you are not in HD - so far Bhargav has said that he&#x2019;ll join from Santa Cruz, so just let me know and I&#x2019;ll contact you as well ;)&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Sunday, 11 April 2010&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
