<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20160306" date="2016-03-06 10:02:38 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Tough summer - but no complaints! &lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>It&#x2019;s not over yet...</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Sorry... it's been a loooooong time but my excuse is that my summer has been really hectic - and it's not over yet. I just realized that I haven't blogged since before I left for State College and NYC - &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MZh10Ez0op8&amp;NR=1"&gt;baaaad monkey&lt;/a&gt;! So there is indeed a lot to write about, so I probably won't mage to get everything in here - well I can give it a try:&#xD;&#xD;- Went to Penn State @ State College: great conference&#xD;&#xD;- Then 5 days in NYC: Awesome - my feet were completely destroyed&#xD;&#xD;- Got back. Two days in HD: Semi-hard work&#xD;&#xD;- Flew to DK for a couple of weeks: Took my Open Water Scuba Diver's license more awesomeness!&#xA0;Working, family parties/dinners en masse - great time.&#xD;&#xD;- Back to HD to exploit the summer visitor period @ MPIA, which is really one of the best times on a year to be (over)productive - despite the awesome weather outside.&#xD;&#xD;- My Brother visited: Drinking, relaxing, scuba diving in a way to filthy and cold lake, some more relaxing and good food.&#xD;&#xD;- Then a weeks worth more of exploiting the visitors at MPIA&#xD;&#xD;- Mette visits - happy days - &#xA0;6 days in Barcelona - great city - back... Mette leaves&#xD;&#xD;- Back to work - hard work; submitted my first proposal (fingers crossed).&#xD;&#xD;and suddenly it's end of august and I'm blogging again before I leave for a weeks conference in Belfast. I will get back for a weeks of summer school in Heidelberg afterwards - looking forward to see the ELIXIR colleagues again - and then a quick meeting at Yale, before it's back to full-time work again.&#xD;&#xD;.&#xD;.&#xD;.&#xD;&#xD;So don't tell me that I'm too lazy to write in here - I feel that my excuse is kind of valid; or? Well, it seems that I managed to get everything listed after all... maybe not with that much detail, but I'm busy. I can give you a couple of highlights if you like (and I remember - my brain is getting old and wrinkly). If you want some pictures with the stories, take a look at my web gallery - this blog will be one of the boring just-text-ones (lazy again).&#xD;&#xD;So, one thing I definitely want to highlight is my trip to New York. As I wrote last time, I was looking forward to it like a kid and was actually a bit scared that NYC couldn't live up to my expectations. Well; no problems there. New York is probably the coolest place I've been. The vibe there was god damn awesome - no kiddin'! Gisella (one of my colleagues, who also went to the Penn State conference) and I had booked a hostel in the Chelsea neighborhood for a fairly okay price. We (or rather I) had a long list of things I wanted to see and do, and despite us only being there for five days we really managed to do A LOT. We basically left the hostel every morning at around 9ish and got back at midnight; completely exhausted and high on experiences. I don't know what was the best and worst we did, so it's hard to pick out anything in particular. Nevertheless, The Circle Line boat trip around Manhattan was a great way to experience the city. The view over the evening streets from Empire State Building - definitely also worth sharing (check out the pics). And then last but not least - times square... that was crazy - a tourist trap - but still pretty spectacular. It was god damn daylight 24-7! Among the other stuff we did (thanks for taken me places I would never have gone myself Gisella - that was awesome!) we had NYC hotdogs at a stand, saw Phantom of the Opera in the Majestic Theater, went to MOMA (I actually like art I realize) and the Museum of Natural History, strolled through central park and the high line park, down 5th and up broadway, had oysters at grand central station, enjoyed the skyline view from both top of the rock (at day) and empire state (at night), walked on Brooklyn bridge and saw the Chrysler, Flatiron and Guggenheim buildings, Watch a NYC Royal ballet, had lunch in china town and dinner in little Italy, mourned at five points and at ground, sailed around the statue of liberty, and of course went shopping. So I feel that we made quite some tick marks on the long to-do lists!&#xD;&#xD;Another thing which I want to brag about, is my new earned 'ability' (or at least I have a certificate from PADI that I've done it) to scuba dive. When I went to DK I (finally, after almost 2 years of trying to find a suitable date) took my OWD license. I had 5 pool dives and 5 open water dives, one of which went to 18... that's a whole new world and I'm really looking forward to start exploring it. When Martin was hear I had beforehand found a place on the web where we could scuba dive in a lake pretty close to here. Unfortunately the seeing was like 1 meter and the water was extremely cold below 6 meters, so it was not exactly what we expected - but it was still fun to try. My plan was that I also wanted to dive in Barcelona, but the place I found on the web unfortunately wasn't open when I went there, so in the end I just spend the time with Mette.&#xD;&#xD;So yeah, Mette and I went to Barcelona for 6 days of relaxing/shopping/city vacation. I could spend a couple of sentences on how great a city Barcelona is, but right after having talked about the mother of cities, NYC, Barcelona would just look like a joke - but it is indeed an great city, and is definitely recommendable. Check out the pictures if you don't believe me ;)&#xD;&#xD;I think that's it for this time. I have to pack before I fly to Belfast monday morning. Unfortunately I won't have much time for sight seeing there, since it will be mostly work - but I will try to see if I get time to stroll down falls road just to do some sight seeing&#xA0;(despite the university buildings which should be pretty cool themselves). I think that will be pretty cool. Talk to you in a couple of weeks (I don't hope it takes as long this time, but I won't promise anything).&#xD;&#xD;cheers&#xD;/K&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Saturday, 28 August 2010&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="28_Its_not_over_yet..._files/shapeimage_2.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="481px" height="314px"/>
</content>
