<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog</title>
    <link>http://kasperschmidt.github.io/Schmidt/Blog</link>
    <description>
</description>
    <item>
      <title>Long time no see</title>
      <link>http://kasperschmidt.github.io/Schmidt/Blog/Entries/2013/2/22_Long_time_no_see.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a7be4b2-df91-4d5a-8652-fe89ca3372cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 05:16:58 +0100</pubDate>
      <description>Time&#x2019;s flying. Haven&#x2019;t had the time to post here as life has been crazy busy here since Christmas. January started out with a remote observing run as I described last time. This meant that there was plenty to do at work. On top of that Mette&#x2019;s sister and cousin passed by in January for a couple of weeks. This meant a couple of days in San Francisco incl. Alcatraz, roadtrip down the pacific coast highway and death valley, as well as a short stop at Las Vegas and Hoover damn. All recommendable and pretty darn amazing :) The second week they were here was a bit more relaxed just chillin&#x2019; in SB, hiking and eating well.&lt;br/&gt;After they left SB we had a couple of weeks before the next visit which we spent finding ourselves again. Then in the beginning of february Mette&#x2019;s parents came. It was there first major trip outside Europe so we were kind of nervous about them traveling here. But everything went fine, and even though the time difference and the long trip was tough on them they made it here without any problems (more than we can say about their return-flight were they had to run in SF to catch their connection to Europe - but luckily they did). Mette&#x2019;s parents were also here for 2 weeks. As opposed to when Mette&#x2019;s sister and cousin were here we spent most of the time in Santa Barbara. We drove to Solvang one day, went for a hike and spent a day in L.A. - well not really L.A. as we were on Venice Beach and IKEA Carson - but besides that we just enjoyed lovely SB. &lt;br/&gt;Before Mette&#x2019;s parents arrived we managed to put the last of our things (mirrors, kitchen rack, pictures etc.) so all we needed to get 110% settled were some smaller things which we picked up in IKEA and getting our lamps up. Mette&#x2019;s dad helped with that (well actually he did everything himself - I got home from work one evening and they were up - sweet!) meaning that we are now fully functional with lamps, mirrors and everything. Great!!&lt;br/&gt;H&amp;amp;J left this tuesday, and despite a large delay from SB they got back to DK safe and sound.&lt;br/&gt;Hubble proposals and Bayesian inference has taken most of my time this week so nothing crazy to report on that. This weekend will probably also be fairly work-heavy but the weather should be nice so I&#x2019;m pretty sure I will take a couple of hours in the sun in our new comfy-porch-chairs; we&#x2019;re livin&#x2019; in sunny Cali&#x2019; after all :)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Cheers&lt;br/&gt;KBS&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Btw. Mette and I are flying to DK for a couple of weeks on March 23rd. So in case you are up for grabbing a coffee, dinner, cup of tea, lunch, beer, or whatever from the 24th onwards. Let us know...&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object200.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://kasperschmidt.github.io/Schmidt/Blog/Entries/2013/2/22_Long_time_no_see.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exposing......</title>
      <link>http://kasperschmidt.github.io/Schmidt/Blog/Entries/2013/1/2_Exposing.......html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc94a88d-b364-4080-ae28-72c74b20907e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 2 Jan 2013 13:19:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <description>Happy new year everyone and belated happy Xmas. While we are collecting photons and the data from yesterday is being reduced I have some time to kill so thought I would say high as I didn&#x2019;t manage to over christmas. However, first of all let me take the opportunity to point everyone to the fact that I moved my website and blog to a new location at the UCSB server last week. So if you are a regular visitor (or want to become one) make sure you update your bookmarks accordingly. The main page can now be found at &lt;a href="http://www.physics.ucsb.edu/~kschmidt/"&gt;www.physics.ucsb.edu/~kschmidt/&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br/&gt;As always December just got started before it was over. Most of the time I spent preparing observations with MOSFIRE on &lt;a href="http://keckobservatory.org/"&gt;Keck&lt;/a&gt;. Yesterday night and now (exposing as I write ;) When I was not working Mette and I were trying to wrap our heads about celebrating christmas in sunny California. Luckily, this year December was apparently above-average grey, wet and chilly so the transition from a cold and wet danish/german December wasn&#x2019;t extreme. Nevertheless, it has been pretty weird with days of no need for a jacket in December - but as most other things over here we are slowly getting used to them. &lt;br/&gt;Initially we were afraid not to get in the right christmas spirit this year but thanks to the overwhelming amount of christmas cards and gifts people send over here we managed to get in the right mood for the holidays. Before we knew we would get so many greetings from back home we tried to care of the mood ourselves, by going to the &#x2018;Parades of Lights&#x2019; festival (a parade of boats &#x2018;dressed&#x2019; in christmas lights) in the harbor where Santa was listening to kids&#x2019; wishes and to see the Nutcracker in one of the theaters on State St. Both events were pretty cool and also helped reminding us that it was about to be christmas.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;On christmas eve we went out for dinner after having spent most of the day Skyping with people back home (It was pretty convenient that we could chime in at european evening-time and then had the rest of the day to ourselves), and after a long walk on the beach and a short dive in the Pacific; well for me that is.&lt;br/&gt;The rest of the christmas vacation we spent mostly relaxing and enjoying life here in SB.&lt;br/&gt;New years eve 2012 was very different in many ways. One thing is that we are here... another the fact that we had been awarded time with MOSFIRE on the night between December 31st and January 1st as well as the night between January 1st and 2nd (now). As it was new years eve Mette decided to join me in the remote observing room at the University for the whole night. At midnight we went to the 6th floor where there is a great view towards the city to see the fireworks. We had noticed that nothing was going on in the days before the 31st - it was not like in DK where people test their fireworks well in advance of new years eve - so we were curious to see if people actually had anything for new years eve... and they didn&#x2019;t!! We were outside looking towards the city from 23:55 to 0010 and we saw 1; yes ONE rocket?!?! That&#x2019;s just crazy (and extremely disappointing). The only semi-sane explanation we can come up with is that it must be illegal to handle fireworks without a permit... but at least the city could then have put something together. But no - there was nothing at all. Hence, new years eve turned pretty quiet this year - maybe we&#x2019;ll take revenge when going into 2014.&lt;br/&gt;Think that was it for this time. The next couple of weeks will be busy; Mette&#x2019;s sister and cousin are flying in on Saturday after a stop in San Francisco. It&#x2019;s gonna be pretty neat to have them here and to experience a bit of the country side with them.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Till next time&lt;br/&gt;K&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object201.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://kasperschmidt.github.io/Schmidt/Blog/Entries/2013/1/2_Exposing.......html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back to &#x2018;everyday life&#x2019;</title>
      <link>http://kasperschmidt.github.io/Schmidt/Blog/Entries/2012/12/7_Back_to_everyday_life.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ab012eb-9531-42f6-922e-30502ef4ff45</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 8 Dec 2012 07:13:44 +0100</pubDate>
      <description>I got back safe and sound from Leiden a couple of weeks ago. Since then life he in SB has been pretty busy. Basically right after I got back Mette and I got our first visit from DK. Mette&#x2019;s Cousin SS passed by. She didn&#x2019;t come directly from DK, as she&#x2019;s spending a couple of months on Hawaii at a language/athletics-school of some kind. They got the week around thanksgiving off and she therefore decided to fly over an say hi. She arrived safely early sunday. Tuesday Mette and her took the bus to L.A. On the wednesday we went to our first UCSB college-basket game. It was Gauchos against UC San Diego, but despite the local team-up there was not a huge turnout as it was the wednesday before thanksgiving. That aside it was a pretty good match (Gauchos won) and the hotdogs were awesome - nothing like trashy food at sports events :)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Originally Mette and I didn&#x2019;t plan anything special for thanksgiving as we were just expecting to be the two of us. But with SS&#x2019;s visit we decided to go all-in and do the whole shebang. I therefore googled &#x2018;traditional thanksgiving dinner&#x2019; and basically cooked what came up. When we realized what such a dinner actually includes we decided to go for a long walk before engaging in the feast. We went to the old mission here in Santa Barbara. I was there the first time I visited so I knew we were in for a treat. And as the weather was gorgeous it turned out to be a great trip. We also passed by the museum of natural history to see the blue way skeleton they have put on display outside - pretty impressive! When we got back the ladies rented Pretty Woman on the Apple TV, as they wanted to re-live their day in L.A. through the eyes of a &#x2018;champagne girl&#x2019; from the nineties... I guess. Well while they were enjoying a combo of cosy rugs, ice cream, Roberts and Gere I enjoyed my new gas stove, a couple of beers (I needed beer for the gravy so I had no choice but drink the rest) and lots of cooking. We ate around 8p.m. (rather late for a usual thanksgiving dinner - but at least it was dinner and not lunch) and the food turned out pretty darn good if I must say myself. Of course there are improvements to be made next year, but for a first timer I&#x2019;m pretty satisfied... and most importantly so were the girls.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;After a couple of days off around thanksgiving SS flew back to Hawaii sunday. That also meant that Mette and I could get back to our daily life with the little twist that we were quickly heading towards December. The whole thanksgiving week the weather was great, but basically all of last week it was gray and foggy with quite some rain (SB-standard). This wasn&#x2019;t actually that bad as it made it seem more wintery and all the christmas decorations going up after thanksgiving didn&#x2019;t seem that weird... even though we still have to get used not wearing thick clothes in December. Last friday we also went to the yearly christmas parade here in Santa Barbara to get the christmas spirit going even more. It was apparently the 60th anniversary. Nice tradition - nothing spectacular but very cosy... and there was firetrucks, cheerleader, marching bands and an old police car;)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Oh yeah and we bough bikes! It&#x2019;s so great not to be dependent on walking around, but actually having the possibility of just jumping on the bike. We exploited that last weekend where we went to the market and to whole foods in just less than ~3 hours. The bike ride to whole foods itself only took half the time the (long) frequent bus takes. So the new bikes are definitely worth the money!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This week has been pretty quiet - just working, running a bit and enjoying good food in the evenings. Tonight I&#x2019;m spending the evening and night at the University (sorry Mette) as AS and PJM have a run at &lt;a href="http://keckobservatory.org/"&gt;Keck&lt;/a&gt; and I&#x2019;m chiming in. Hence, I&#x2019;m not actually actually observing I&#x2019;m just sitting in as preparation for later this month and next year where we have time on Keck and are doing our own observations, which I&#x2019;m really looking forward to. So far the night has been okay. A couple of hick-ups, but nothing AS and PJM couldn&#x2019;t handle... but now some clouds are unfortunately moving in (hence some time to blog). Let&#x2019;s see how goes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Cheers&lt;br/&gt;K&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object202.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://kasperschmidt.github.io/Schmidt/Blog/Entries/2012/12/7_Back_to_everyday_life.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Furnished place - yes sir!</title>
      <link>http://kasperschmidt.github.io/Schmidt/Blog/Entries/2012/11/14_Furnished_place_-_yes_sir%21.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e2016d0c-e417-4693-a2af-b2107a533651</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 18:03:12 +0100</pubDate>
      <description>So a couple of weeks flew by again. As I&#x2019;m writing this I&#x2019;m somewhere over the east coast on my way back from the Netherlands where we held the last ELIXIR meeting monday and tuesday. But more about that below, as I have to give my probs to IKEA and Walmart first.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As I mentioned last time we ordered a whole bunch of stuff from IKEA and a couch from Walmart and last week everything got delivered. It&#x2019;s incredible how much you appreciates a damn couch and a dining table when you have lived with only a bed, chairs and a small table for almost 2 months. We spent a couple of days getting everything put together (it is kind of a puzzle when you have larger furniture from IKEA) and only one small thing was missing. Luckily it was nothing important (a &#x2018;lock&#x2019; for the dinner-table-extensions) so I must say that I&#x2019;m grateful to both IKEA and Walmart for being so corporative... well IKEA didn&#x2019;t really do much except for handing over the goods to their carrier. But nevertheless, it&#x2019;s great to have a furnished place :) Therefore it won&#x2019;t be long before I post some pictures; but in case you haven&#x2019;t realized I&#x2019;m trying to upload real-time updates on Instagram (usr: kabosc) and FB.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Last week was not only exciting because of the furniture delivery. It was also the week where I got a crash-course in the new projects I&#x2019;m gonna work on the next years. I already knew kind of what it was about (spectroscopic confirmation of redshift 8 galaxy candidates from the &lt;a href="https://wolf359.colorado.edu/"&gt;BoRG survey&lt;/a&gt;), but last week L. Bradley and M. Trenti (he&#x2019;s actually also here this week) passed by UCSB to get me up to speed on the project(s). There was A LOT of information to absorb and frustration with some of the code, but in the big picture it was extremely useful to have both of them hanging around and burying me in info on the project. As this was really useful it was also a pity that I had to &#x2018;run off&#x2019; to Leiden last saturday, but this had been planned for quite some time.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The reason I had to fly to Leiden, was as mentioned, that we had the last ELIXIR meeting (the Marie Curie network I was payed by during most of my time in Heidelberg). This also means that I haven&#x2019;t fully enjoyed the furnished place yet... but I&#x2019;ll have plenty of time to do that when I get back tonight :)&lt;br/&gt;Well; even though the timing of the meeting was rather inconvenient it was great to see all the &#x2018;usual suspects&#x2019; again. &lt;br/&gt;The meeting program was rather short so there was plenty time to be social - which was only fair as this was the last meeting of the network. To finish the whole thing of we (all the students) went out for one last lunch yesterday before a bunch of us took the train to Amsterdam. No tears but still kind of weird that none of us have any clue when and where we&#x2019;ll meet again. In Amsterdam I had time to pass by &lt;a href="http://www.iamsterdam.com/en-GB/Ndtrc/Concerto"&gt;Concerto&lt;/a&gt; - probably the best record store I have been to - for the third time ;) Some people go to Amsterdam to get high on weed or women; I get high on music there!&lt;br/&gt;Before the actual program started monday and tuesday I spend sunday with JR and his boys. A very grown-up but awesome day!! We managed to get the boys away from the tv and biked with them to a nearby playground (it was not raining - we even saw the sun!). After that we went grocery shopping in the most kids-friendly supermarket I have ever been to. They had singing cows and pigs to entertain the kids, shopping carts formed as F1 racers, bouncing castle and slides - pretty neat place. In the evening it was &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/St._Martin's_Day"&gt;St. Martin&#x2019;s day&lt;/a&gt;. This means that dutch kids go &#x2018;trick-or-treat&#x2019;. They are not dressed up as for halloween but carry small lanterns and sing songs for the people who open. We met with a bunch of other parents from the neighborhood, who seemed to have been coordinating this evening for a while. At 1800 hours hell broke loose. From basically all houses small kids with lanterns ran to the street in a quest for filling their bags with candy. Even JR didn&#x2019;t realize that so many kids lived in their neighborhood. It lasted for about an hour and the boys seemed pretty satisfied with their &#x2018;candy-catch&#x2019;. We went back to JR&#x2019;s place cooked some dinner which JR had to force the boys to eat before they dived into their catch of the night.&lt;br/&gt;Before sunday I wasn&#x2019;t sure if the &#x2018;sugar-rush&#x2019; term was invented by parents to prevent kids from having too much candy, or if it was actually real... now I&#x2019;m not in doubt any more. The energy level of the boys exploded; they were chasing one another, eating candy, breakdancing, eating candy, shouting, eating candy, laughing, eating candy, fighting, eating candy, singing, and eating even more candy until they looked like they were over-dozing and went into something looking like a trance or coma of some kind. Pretty neat :) JR even said monday morning that his kids were hungover when they woke up. So &#x2018;sugar-rush&#x2019; is definitely real. Thanks for a great day mate!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Well; think that&#x2019;s it for now. I think I&#x2019;ll manage to watch a last movie before we land in Houston and I have to find my flight to L.A. Am really looking forward to get home. 6 flights (adding up to ~25 hours in the air) in just 5 days is a bit too much. But after all it was worth it.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Cheers,&lt;br/&gt;Kasper&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Oh by the way - check out what Mette and I found in SEARS the other day... I think we know where to get our plastic christmas tree for this year - not!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object203.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://kasperschmidt.github.io/Schmidt/Blog/Entries/2012/11/14_Furnished_place_-_yes_sir%21.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <iweb:dateFormat>EEEE, d MMMM y</iweb:dateFormat>
    <iweb:baseURL>http://kasperschmidt.github.io/Schmidt/Blog</iweb:baseURL>
    <iweb:maximumSummaryItems>4</iweb:maximumSummaryItems>
  </channel>
</rss>
