<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="891CD9C4-0A73-4D6E-A6C5-B4F69B72674F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20121225" date="2012-12-26 03:44:27 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Cox... you can still make up for it!&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Internet at home still pending.</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Back to work. As you can see above I have already managed to make my office cozy - kind of. Even though the office is in the middle of the building so there are no windows to outside I actually like it - then I can concentrate on what I&#x2019;m there for. But besides starting to get up to speed on new projects I have nothing special to report yet. &#xD;But our tv antennae arrived... when I first unwrapped it I saw to my bitter surprise that it was a coax antenna, and as we shipped our danish tv over here it uses the european standard RV input. Hence I spent the weekend hunting down a coax-to-RV adaptor. I found one at Radioschack which costed basically the same as the antenna - but without it the antenna would be useless. Well either way, I got home and plugged in the antenna but unfortunately this didn&#x2019;t result in us having more channels. We just have a better signal on ABC. It appears that ABC is the only channel we can catch the old-fashioned way here so no NFL at home for me:&#x2019;( well then I just have to watch college football when I&#x2019;m home and find a bar when I want to watch some NFL I guess.&#xD;With the antenna the new modem for our internet also arrived. But this didn&#x2019;t go easy either. Last wednesday the Cox cable guy showed up while I was at work and (supposedly) turned on the internet connection. When I got the modem last week I tried to hook it up but there was no signal what-so-ever, so friday morning I called Cox to hear if they could please send out another cable guy to make sure everything was fine. At first the guy I talked with was kind of cocky and just said &#x2018;do this&#x2019; and &#x2018;do that&#x2019;. However, as I&#x2019;m not a complete idiot with electronics (if I have to say myself ;) I had already tried his solutions and he finally arrived at the same conclusion as me, namely that there is no signal. At first they could only send out a guy tomorrow, i.e., 5 days after I talked with them, but he called me back after two hours and said he scheduled a guy for sunday evening. Sweet - nice guy to actually ask them to pass by on a sunday to fix it... well it was indeed too good to be true. I was home waiting for the cable guy but he never showed up so I&#x2019;m still without (our own - the landlord has been so kind to lend us his wireless until we get ours fixed) internet at home. When I called them they couldn&#x2019;t help me (this time the guy I talked to was not even trying to be helpful) and all they could see was that I had an appointment tomorrow. So now I just hope they can fix it tomorrow as promised - you can still make up for you incompetence Cox Cable, but my patience is running out...&#xD;Well enough bad vibes for this time! Besides finding and adapter to the tv-antenna I went to Santa Barbara Farmers Market this saturday, and damn that&#x2019;s great. I&#x2019;m pretty sure we will spent quite some tuesdays and saturdays stocking up on fresh vegetables here. One has to watch out, but in-between there are actually some really good deals. And rumor has it that they sell very cheap shellfish sometimes - gotta look out for that!&#xD;Sunday Anna had invited some people to a BBQ at Goleta Beach Park to celebrate her birthday. Pretty neat to meet some more people and a great occasion to hang out with some of my new colleagues. The sky was clear, the beer cold, the ribs awesome, and the burgers great. Combining that with several &#x2018;games&#x2019; and a bit of football-trowing makes for a great sunday (besides the fact I had to leave early just to get home to wait for a cable guy that never showed up... but enough said about that). I&#x2019;m already looking forward to the next one!&#xD;Yesterday we were a couple of people who met to play some (Taiwanese apparently - I didn&#x2019;t know there was a difference before we had to refresh our memory regarding the rules yesterday) &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mahjong"&gt;Mahjong&lt;/a&gt;. We learned it a couple of weeks ago by Sherry and her mom. Unfortunately Sherry left the department last week so now we are on our own. It&#x2019;s a pretty cool game even though we haven&#x2019;t explored it&#x2019;s full potential yet - for instance we have no clue about the point/scoring system yet... but it&#x2019;s not the last time we have played for sure!&#xD;And one last (but certainly not least) thing before it&#x2019;s bedtime: Mette is arriving tomorrow evening. Brilliant!!&#xD;&#xD;See you around.&#xD;BS&#xD;&#xD;Oh and by the way, as I have no clue about who&#x2019;s actually reading my blog posts (besides my parents of course - thanks;) and since I&#x2019;m curios by nature, I will start adding a Facebook recommendation/like button to my posts. Both to see who drops bye (if they care to like/recommend the post) but also to enable people to spread the word and comment on my posts via Facebook. Let&#x2019;s see how it goes... ready... set... like...&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Tuesday, 9 October 2012&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="9_Internet_%40_home_still_pending._files/shapeimage_2.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="450px" height="231px"/>
</content>
